欢迎来到共和党图形模型的另一堂课，所以我们在总结
welcome to another class on Republican graphical models so we were summarizing
graphical models so we were summarizing basically an example of reduction three
基本上是归约三种算法的一个例子，所以在我讨论之前
basically an example of reduction three algorithms so before I discussed the
algorithms so before I discussed the example once more I wanted to remind you
再次举例，我想提醒您的是
example once more I wanted to remind you the message passing that is applied by
the message passing that is applied by the junction tree algorithm and there is
联结树算法，不幸的是，这里我可能没有原理图
the junction tree algorithm and there is no unfortunately schematic here I may
no unfortunately schematic here I may need to add the schematic but basically
需要添加原理图，但基本上我们有一个情况
need to add the schematic but basically what we have is we have a situation
what we have is we have a situation where I have one you know one maximal
我有一个人，你知道一个最大的派系，我们称其为V到左边，
where I have one you know one maximal clique that we call it V to the left and
clique that we call it V to the left and another W to the right in between them
在它们之间右边的另一个W处，我们有分隔符s，所以这个想法是
another W to the right in between them we have the separator s so the idea was
we have the separator s so the idea was passing messages from V to W in a
从V到W向前传递消息，此等式位于顶部
passing messages from V to W in a forward manner this equation on the top
forward manner this equation on the top and then on reversed passing messages
然后反向通过分隔符将消息从W传递回我
and then on reversed passing messages from W back to me through the separator
from W back to me through the separator so I want to review with you the
因此，我想与您一起审查问题，以便我们尝试查看此问题
so I want to review with you the question so then we will try to see this
question so then we will try to see this in a very specific example on what
在一个非常具体的示例中，我们将详细说明如果您尝试这样做的话
in a very specific example on what exactly we tried to do so if you
exactly we tried to do so if you remember the separator involves the
记住分隔符涉及两个V共同的变量
remember the separator involves the variables that they are common to both V
variables that they are common to both V and W so obviously to show me initially
和W显然是为了告诉我最初将分隔器电位初始化为1
and W so obviously to show me initially initialize the separator potentials to 1
initialize the separator potentials to 1 ok so obviously to update the separator
好，很显然，要更新分离器的潜力，我们必须整合所有
ok so obviously to update the separator potentials we have to integrate out all
potentials we have to integrate out all the volume Wilson V except the very much
音量Wilson V除外，除了分离器中的很大部分，所以Ross V小调
the volume Wilson V except the very much in the separator right so Ross V minor
in the separator right so Ross V minor says they are not relevant information
说它们不是与W相关的信息，所以我们必须将它们集成到一起
says they are not relevant information for W so we have to integrate them out
for W so we have to integrate them out so this is pissed R subscript s means
所以这很生气R下标s表示分隔器的电位是
so this is pissed R subscript s means the potential of the separator is this
the potential of the separator is this then we go to W and we update the
然后我们转到W，然后更新最大派系W的势
then we go to W and we update the potential of the maximal clique W by
potential of the maximal clique W by multiplying by this factor of the
乘以更新的分隔器电位的该因子除以
multiplying by this factor of the updated separator potential divided by
updated separator potential divided by the original separator potential and
原始分隔符的潜力，显然在您启动算法时
the original separator potential and obviously when you start the algorithm
obviously when you start the algorithm first is equal to one in the process
首先等于一个，在我们一直被征税的过程中，确实很棒
first is equal to one in the process we've been tax really great
we've been tax really great so the objective just to be consistent
所以目标是保持一致，因为所有事物都有一颗恒星
so the objective just to be consistent because everything has one star the
because everything has one star the updated cyber cyber star is equal to
更新后的网络网络明星等于我们开始的原始II型
updated cyber cyber star is equal to original the type II that we started
original the type II that we started with right now in the propagation of
现在正在将消息从W传播回V
with right now in the propagation of messages from W back to V so we are
messages from W back to V so we are going to update the separator potential
将以W和W的电势开始更新分隔器电势
going to update the separator potential by starting with the potential of W and
by starting with the potential of W and you've never lost the ability potential
您将永远不会失去我们在这里计算出的能力潜能，我们将
you've never lost the ability potential that we computed here and we're gonna
that we computed here and we're gonna integrate you have pretty valuable
整合您的资源，除了台式机外，其他都非常有价值，然后我们将转到
integrate you have pretty valuable except desktop then we're going to go to
except desktop then we're going to go to the potential of the click V and take
单击V的电位并取先前的值，即
the potential of the click V and take the previous value which is this and
the previous value which is this and update it began by multiplying with this
更新开始时先乘以这三颗双星除以进站
update it began by multiplying with this three double star divided by pitstop
three double star divided by pitstop alright so this is the new value of the
好吧，这是分隔符的新值除以旧值
alright so this is the new value of the separator divided by the old value the
separator divided by the old value the new value is this the old values what we
新值是我们在上一步中计算出的旧值
new value is this the old values what we computed on the previous step as we go
computed on the previous step as we go from V to W and a mystic process again W
从V到W再到一个神秘的过程W并没有改变方程，看起来很奇怪
from V to W and a mystic process again W doesn't change the equations look weird
doesn't change the equations look weird but what is interesting is when we do
但有趣的是，当我们执行此更新时，计算结果为
but what is interesting is when we do this update the the calculations are
this update the the calculations are consistent consistent in the sense that
从某种意义上说是一致的，如果您计算间隔
consistent consistent in the sense that if you calculate the separation
if you calculate the separation potential by starting with this click
通过单击此W的潜在值，您可以对平均值进行积分
potential by starting with this click for W and you integrate average
for W and you integrate average everything out except s1 if you start
如果您以V开头并进行积分，则除s1以外的所有内容
everything out except s1 if you start with a click of V and you integrate
with a click of V and you integrate everything out except s this is equal to
除了s之外的所有东西都等于腐烂，所以结果
everything out except s this is equal to rot so result
rot so result consistent secure at the end of the day
在一天结束时计算分离器电势时保持一致的安全性
consistent secure at the end of the day the separator potential is calculated
the separator potential is calculated uniquely there's no double star shared
唯一没有共享双星，因为您还记得旁边的双星
uniquely there's no double star shared because you remember side double star
because you remember side double star maybe I should put it to look nicer side
也许我应该把它看起来更好一点侧面双星W等于的PI星
maybe I should put it to look nicer side double star W is equal to PI star of
double star W is equal to PI star of that be okay and another thing that we
没关系，我们提到的另一件事是
that be okay and another thing that we mentioned was that both in the forward
mentioned was that both in the forward and the backward swept the joint
并向后扫
and the backward swept the joint probability distribution of both the
probability distribution of both the variables in the junction tree remains
联结树中的变量在物理上保持不变，我知道了
variables in the junction tree remains invariant physically okay and I have I
invariant physically okay and I have I don't think we missed a premium example
不要以为我们错过了一个优质的示例，右键单击会说是另外一个示例
don't think we missed a premium example right click will say be here another
right click will say be here another colleague would be ste so actually you
同事将是ste，因此实际上您可以将此作为一个简单的示例
colleague would be ste so actually you can take this as a simple example of the
can take this as a simple example of the previous case that I held so before we
在我们拥有宝马之前，我曾持有过这样的案例，所以这是a和B WS b n3
previous case that I held so before we have BMW so this here is a and B WS b n3
have BMW so this here is a and B WS b n3 and the separator is b so that i am
分隔符是b，所以我在这里很简单地向您展示
and the separator is b so that i am showing you here with a very simple
showing you here with a very simple calculation is that each step in the
计算过程中的每个步骤基本上都会保留所有影响
calculation is that each step in the process all effects basically remains
process all effects basically remains the same
没关系，所以我们不是真的在玩
the same alright so we're not really playing with
alright so we're not really playing with the joint distribution and a simple
联合分配和向前一步的简单证明是
the joint distribution and a simple proof in the forward step is the
proof in the forward step is the following if you calculate size style of
如果您将尺寸样式计算为V乘以W的y星除以
following if you calculate size style of V times y star of W divided by the
V times y star of W divided by the separator potential star but the way I
分隔符潜在的星号，但我在联结树中提醒您的方式是
separator potential star but the way I remind you in a junction tree because
remind you in a junction tree because originally we started with the stability
最初我们以等于1的稳定潜力开始，我们隐藏了关节
originally we started with the stability potential equal to 1 we hide the Joint
potential equal to 1 we hide the Joint Distribution as the product of the
作为所有集团潜在潜力的产物进行分配
Distribution as the product of the potentials of all the cliques in the
potentials of all the cliques in the numerator divided by the product of the
分子除以所有分离器的电势乘积
numerator divided by the product of the potentials of all the separators so we
potentials of all the separators so we don't double count effectively for the
不要对分隔符有效地进行重复计数，因为
don't double count effectively for the separator right because
separator right because we have two potentials that say V and W
我们有两个势能说V和W对，它们服务于分隔符
we have two potentials that say V and W right and they serve the separator
right and they serve the separator potential so we divide by that of course
势，所以我们首先除以那当然等于等于回答它的
potential so we divide by that of course initially this is equal to answer it's
initially this is equal to answer it's not an issue but I wanted to show you
这不是问题，但我想向您展示，这剩下的续集
not an issue but I wanted to show you that this remaining sequel to the
that this remaining sequel to the original joint probability distribution
每一步的原始联合概率分布，我们可以在这里看到
original joint probability distribution at every step and we can see it here in
at every step and we can see it here in the forward step so if I calculate this
前进的步骤，所以如果我在这里计算此数量，然后我在旁边停了下来
the forward step so if I calculate this quantity here and I stopped you beside
quantity here and I stopped you beside this table I remind you besides star
这张桌子我提醒你，除了前进时，星星不会改变，所以
this table I remind you besides star doesn't change on the forward step so
doesn't change on the forward step so it's I've a the update of side W is the
这是我的W面的更新是网站W乘以子J因子
it's I've a the update of side W is the website W times the sub J factor with
website W times the sub J factor with the new separator potential divided by
将新的分离器电势除以旧时间，然后在T星和PR中尝试使用W
the new separator potential divided by the old times try W so in T star and P R
the old times try W so in T star and P R star cancel out and basically what you
明星抵消，基本上你得到的是你得到联合概率
star cancel out and basically what you get is you get the joint probability
get is you get the joint probability distribution that we started with so
如此有效地开始进行分配操作的分布
distribution that we started with so effectively the do manipulations of the
effectively the do manipulations of the potentials for the maximal cliques and
最大集团和分隔器的潜力，但在此过程中会起火
potentials for the maximal cliques and the separators but in the process fire
the separators but in the process fire effects remain the same so we will see
效果保持不变，因此我们将看到一个示例，它的确切形式
effects remain the same so we will see an example what exactly form this
an example what exactly form this potential take with a very simple case
一个非常简单的案例可能的潜力，但我想我开始讨论这个问题
potential take with a very simple case but I think I started discussing this
but I think I started discussing this one on Tuesday so the example we talking
一个星期二，所以这个例子我们今天讨论的是隐藏模型
one on Tuesday so the example we talking about hidden models today surrounding
about hidden models today surrounding maybe spend two or three lectures so we
也许要花两三堂课，所以我们会做些细节，但是我
maybe spend two or three lectures so we do this sort of in some detail but I
do this sort of in some detail but I won't give you an application of the
不会为您提供隐藏树上的结点树算法的应用程序
won't give you an application of the junction tree algorithm on a hidden
junction tree algorithm on a hidden Markov model so then this is front of
马尔可夫模型，所以这是心理模型上最前沿的
Markov model so then this is front of the most on the mental model for
the most on the mental model for dynamics okay and
动态还可以，这里的想法是我们有一些
dynamics okay and the idea here is we have some
the idea here is we have some observations y0 y1 YT y capital
y0 y1 YT y时间遍历我的意思是我在
observations y0 y1 YT y capital traversal in time I mean I'm
traversal in time I mean I'm interpreting here it's time since we
自从我们谈论动力学以来，这是时候了，但无论如何
interpreting here it's time since we talked about dynamics but to be any
talked about dynamics but to be any sequence to really and this are some
到真正的顺序，这是一些隐藏状态好吗
sequence to really and this are some hidden state okay
hidden state okay and but we don't know what they are and
但是我们不知道它们是什么，所以我们要做的是
and but we don't know what they are and so what we do is we have a dynamical
so what we do is we have a dynamical model in this case a Markovian model
这种情况下的马尔可夫模型，告诉我如何离开国家
model in this case a Markovian model that tells me how I move from the state
that tells me how I move from the state a time that say one to the time 2 and
时间对2说一个，然后我有一个观察模型
a time that say one to the time 2 and then I have an observation model that
then I have an observation model that tells me as which state what's the
告诉我哪个状态的观测概率为y1
tells me as which state what's the probability of observing let's say y1
probability of observing let's say y1 given Q 1 so effectively I have a joint
鉴于Q 1如此有效，我的联合分布看起来又像这样
given Q 1 so effectively I have a joint distribution that looks like this again
distribution that looks like this again we're going to give you a risk
我们将为您提供有关此模型是什么的风险解释
we're going to give you a risk interpretation on what this model is
interpretation on what this model is good right in starting today basically
从今天开始的好权利，基本上也许是我们达成此目标的借口
good right in starting today basically maybe the excuse that we reach this
maybe the excuse that we reach this point but the for now the Joint
要点，但目前联合分配基本上是
point but the for now the Joint Distribution is basically this is a
Distribution is basically this is a directed graph is where you start right
有向图是您正确开始的地方，是初始状态的概率
directed graph is where you start right and the probability of the initial state
and the probability of the initial state and then you have the probability of for
然后您可以根据状态获得预留装载程序的可能性
and then you have the probability of for reservation loaders given the state
reservation loaders given the state which we take them to be independent
我们认为他们是独立的好，所以考虑到Q，这些妻子是
which we take them to be independent okay so given Q these wives are
okay so given Q these wives are independent and the independence comes
独立性，独立性来自于这种分离你可以看到y
independent and the independence comes from this separation you can see that y
from this separation you can see that y 0 to the end of y 1 given this state
0到y 1的末尾给定此状态，因为如果按照这种方式运行，则为
0 to the end of y 1 given this state because if you go this way it is and
because if you go this way it is and this is given the path is blocked here
这是给定的，这里的路径被阻塞了，但是又不是很重要
this is given the path is blocked here all right but again not very important
all right but again not very important for this lecture and then we have the
在本次讲座中，我们将获得这些过渡的结果
for this lecture and then we have the product of these transition
product of these transition probabilities but basically give me how
概率，但是基本上给了我从状态PT到T加1的方式
probabilities but basically give me how from the state PT I go through T plus 1
from the state PT I go through T plus 1 I mean I have a graphical model that has
我的意思是我有一个图形模型，该模型的联合分布看起来像
I mean I have a graphical model that has a joint distribution that looks like
a joint distribution that looks like this and I would like somehow to go and
这和我想以某种方式去应用联结树算法
this and I would like somehow to go and and apply the junction tree algorithm
and apply the junction tree algorithm and see if it sort of makes that now
看看它是否使现在看起来像是正确的
and see if it sort of makes that now this looks like it's saying right even
this looks like it's saying right even though we do have observations so you
尽管我们确实有观察结果，所以您记得变化，我们得出了
though we do have observations so you remember for change we derive the
remember for change we derive the coordinate message this alpha we derive
协调此alpha消息，我们将得出反向消息beta，而我要
coordinate message this alpha we derive the backward messages beta and I'm going
the backward messages beta and I'm going to give you the recursive equations
再给您递归方程式，我们将看到关于
to give you the recursive equations again and we will see that of this about
again and we will see that of this about what the Rama message just as well so
Rama消息也是如此，所以现在的想法是联结树是
what the Rama message just as well so the idea is now the junction tree was
the idea is now the junction tree was going to give us something distant some
会给我们带来一些遥不可及的美国人
going to give us something distant some shape of the Americans were somehow able
shape of the Americans were somehow able love for this trivial problem we give us
热爱这个琐碎的问题，我们给了我们东西，但看上去它们很熟悉
love for this trivial problem we give us things but plate they look very familiar
things but plate they look very familiar interesting actually writes a realized
有趣的是实际上写了一个实现的应用程序来看看我们从中得到什么
interesting actually writes a realized application to see what we get from this
application to see what we get from this model so the joint probability
模型，所以联合概率分布我不会再打扰了
model so the joint probability distribution again I am not gonna bother
distribution again I am not gonna bother actually relations we're going to see
实际的关系，我们将在下周看到这一点，因此
actually relations we're going to see this in in next week so with the
this in in next week so with the junction tree I believe right if we do
如果我们正确地做事并给出一些证据，我相信是正确的
junction tree I believe right if we do things correctly given some evidence so
things correctly given some evidence so given the measurements would say at
鉴于测量结果会表明您可能在不同时间感兴趣
given the measurements would say at different times you may be interested at
different times you may be interested at this time T to calculate the posterior
这次T计算状态TP的后验，这称为
this time T to calculate the posterior of the state TP this is called the
of the state TP this is called the filtering problem maybe if we given some
过滤问题，也许如果我们给定了一些时间s的仪器，我们想
filtering problem maybe if we given some instruments of the time s we want to
instruments of the time s we want to predict ahead the stage but prediction
提前预测阶段，但是预测问题和那些电影问题是，如果我们
predict ahead the stage but prediction problem and those movie problem is if we
problem and those movie problem is if we are using lots of data a past time T can
在过去的时间T中使用大量数据，我们可以返回并计算估算值吗
are using lots of data a past time T can we come back and calculate an estimate
we come back and calculate an estimate of the state together this better more
在一起的状态，从这些过滤后的角度来看，这会更好，更平滑
of the state together this better more smooth from these filtering posterior
smooth from these filtering posterior distribution so this is the smoking
分布，所以这是吸烟问题，这是我的原因之一
distribution so this is the smoking problem this are one of the reasons I
problem this are one of the reasons I want to do this hidden Markov models and
想要多做一些隐藏的马尔可夫模型和状态空间模型
want to do this hidden Markov models and state-space models in a little bit more
state-space models in a little bit more detail right is
详细信息是
即使我在讨论他们，也表现出色，所以这是一个男人
state-space models in a little bit more detail right is
performance even though they I am discussing them therefore it's a men
即使我在讨论他们，也表现出色，所以这是一个男人
discussing them therefore it's a men there are sort of very fundamental
在数据方面存在一些非常基本的问题
there are sort of very fundamental problems in the context of data
problems in the context of data simulation so any of you who works on
模拟，以便您从事解决各种动态问题的任何人
simulation so any of you who works on any sort of dynamical problems from
any sort of dynamical problems from fluid mechanics to weather prediction to
流体力学，可以对地震进行天气预报，无论发生何种振动
fluid mechanics to weather prediction to earthquakes to whatever the vibrations
earthquakes to whatever the vibrations you know this are the problems that you
您知道这是您需要知道如何解决紧急情况的问题
you know this are the problems that you need to know how to address the emergent
need to know how to address the emergent of academic problems they have practical
学术问题，他们有实际问题，至少您需要知道三个
of academic problems they have practical problems at least three you need to know
problems at least three you need to know if somebody asked you what is filtering
如果有人问你，什么正在过滤这种移动的预测，
if somebody asked you what is filtering what's prediction with this moving and
what's prediction with this moving and this topic is self-contained in a way
这个主题是独立的，以至于他们已经三年多了
this topic is self-contained in a way that they have been three years many
that they have been three years many individuals have written which one after
个人写下了一个接一个地重新发现的东西，
individuals have written which one after the other rediscovering things and
the other rediscovering things and dressing them up with nice algebra
用漂亮的代数东西修饰它们，
dressing them up with nice algebra things that they were known in the
things that they were known in the forties and fifties okay but lots of us
四十和五十年代还可以，但是我们很多人都在用新的方式发现这一点
forties and fifties okay but lots of us are in discovering this with new
are in discovering this with new techniques so there hasn't been any
技术，因此40年来一直没有任何重大发展
techniques so there hasn't been any major developments for 40 years or
major developments for 40 years or Cassini whoops don't expect to see
卡西尼号飞车不要期望看到新的东西，只是一样的东西
Cassini whoops don't expect to see something new it's just the same things
something new it's just the same things presently different okay like today I'm
现在像今天一样不一样，我要在路口介绍一下
presently different okay like today I'm going to present this with the junction
going to present this with the junction 3 algorithm I don't think in any of
3种算法，我认为在这些书中都没有，它们实际上带来了
3 algorithm I don't think in any of these books they actually bring the
these books they actually bring the junction tree algorithm because that is
联结树算法，因为这对于做数据的人来说太复杂了
junction tree algorithm because that is too complicated for people who do data
too complicated for people who do data stimulation ok so what I want to do so
刺激好吧，所以我想做的如此粘稠，我们需要一张图表
stimulation ok so what I want to do so viscous the amazement we need a graph
viscous the amazement we need a graph theoretic approach right if for example
理论方法是正确的，例如，如果您想最简单地使用这些方法
theoretic approach right if for example if you want to be simplest of these
if you want to be simplest of these problems that I mentioned before are
我之前提到的问题非常复杂，除非您以某种方式
problems that I mentioned before are very complicated and unless you somehow
very complicated and unless you somehow use conditional independence relations
使用图暗示的条件独立关系以及一种简单的方法
use conditional independence relations implied by the graph and an easy way to
implied by the graph and an easy way to see how complicated calculations would
看看计算有多复杂，例如计算
see how complicated calculations would be look at the calculating for example
be look at the calculating for example the marginal likelihood so if you want
边际可能性，因此，如果您想尝试完成参数中的
the marginal likelihood so if you want to try to to complete parameters in the
to try to to complete parameters in the model like parameters see that if
像参数这样的模型可以看到，如果它们处于状态转换模型或
model like parameters see that if they're in the state transition model or
they're in the state transition model or in the observation model effectively we
有效地在观察模型中，我们必须做某种形式的汽车
in the observation model effectively we have to do some sort of car
have to do some sort of car model evidence by playing with you know
通过与您一起玩来建立模型证据，使这种可能性最大化，这就是
model evidence by playing with you know maximizing this likelihood and that is
maximizing this likelihood and that is this life is within involves integration
这个生命涉及所有所有可能价值的整合
this life is within involves integration over all possible values of all the
over all possible values of all the states at all times so if you have you
随时说明，如果您知道的话，我们这里有大写的T步骤，
states at all times so if you have you know we have capital T steps here and
know we have capital T steps here and each page will take and take M values
每页将取M个值mr。问题M给T供电我不好意思
each page will take and take M values mr. problem M to power T excuse me I
mr. problem M to power T excuse me I mean if P is 4 million and M is 100 you
意思是如果P是400万而M是100
mean if P is 4 million and M is 100 you know then just good luck
know then just good luck cannot do it but with dysgraphia lytic
不能做到这一点，但是借助音像障碍解析方法，您实际上可以做到这一点
cannot do it but with dysgraphia lytic approaches you can actually do this
approaches you can actually do this problem on your little PC okay and and
在您的小型PC上出现问题，我们希望您能做到这一点
problem on your little PC okay and and we hope that you will do this you see as
we hope that you will do this you see as a former problem as well okay in in
一个以前的问题，以及在下周二的细节中还可以，我想
a former problem as well okay in in details next well Tuesday I wanted to
details next well Tuesday I wanted to remind you in the context of what we're
在上下文中提醒您我们将要使用Junction三种算法
remind you in the context of what we're gonna do with Junction three algorithms
gonna do with Junction three algorithms on how the conditional dependence
关于条件依赖关系的定义
on how the conditional dependence relations and the definitions of the
relations and the definitions of the various interest points of interest you
您可以计算出各种兴趣点，例如给定的基础
various interest points of interest you can calculate for example basis given
can calculate for example basis given all of the data Y right this is this
所有数据Y对，这是没有分布，可以为您提供
all of the data Y right this is this nothing distribution gives you the
nothing distribution gives you the probability of P P so what I say
PP的机率，所以我说的援助在时间0到时间是正确的
probability of P P so what I say assistance is right from time 0 to time
assistance is right from time 0 to time capital T so if you can travel all right
大写T，所以如果您知道我的计算方法太好，便可以旅行
capital T so if you can travel all right if you know I'm too nice calculations
if you know I'm too nice calculations that you guys can follow but it comes
你们可以遵循，但是结果就是分配是
that you guys can follow but it comes out this is making distribution is the
out this is making distribution is the product of this joint distribution and
此联合分布的乘积和此条件乘积的乘积
product of this joint distribution and the product of this conditional
the product of this conditional distribution divided by the marginal of
分布除以Y的边际，所以这个传统是
distribution divided by the marginal of Y so this tradition is is the
Y so this tradition is is the probability of observing y0 y1 wealthy a
观察y0 y1富裕的安全性3的权利的概率是多少
probability of observing y0 y1 wealthy a number of safety 3 right and what is
number of safety 3 right and what is nice
很好，这是一个小便观察的时间
nice this is holding a pee-pee observing when
this is holding a pee-pee observing when I pick this one away people are still
我选择这一个离开的人，我仍然会像保真一样好吗，
I pick this one away people are still like fidelity okay in the note that I'm
like fidelity okay in the note that I'm concerned I have not finished them yet
我担心他们还没有完成，尽管那意味着他们
concerned I have not finished them yet though for its immense that meant them
though for its immense that meant them 200 something pages in in some groups
至少今天在某些组中有200多个页面被称为
200 something pages in in some groups this service is called at least today
this service is called at least today when the Condors the Alpha mastered and
当秃鹰掌握了阿尔法之后，这个世界经济迅速发展起来，而你
when the Condors the Alpha mastered and this world economy domestics and you
this world economy domestics and you will see why I call it out from it
将会看到为什么我从alpha调用它，我们将其更改以进行调用
will see why I call it out from it alphas we call it on for change the
alphas we call it on for change the forward message right and bit enough
通过Bella的消息正确而正确地转发消息，使您信服
forward message right and bit enough with message from Bella convinced you
with message from Bella convinced you that this is really requires a forward
这确实需要进行向前计算或在我们向前发展时进行更新
that this is really requires a forward calculation or update as we move forward
calculation or update as we move forward in India hmm and this required backward
在印度，嗯，这需要进行反向计算，所以无论如何我想
in India hmm and this required backward calculations so anyways when I wanted to
calculations so anyways when I wanted to say the definition of alpha in other
说其他书中的alpha定义，而不是由此给出
say the definition of alpha in other books rather than being given by this
books rather than being given by this Joint Distribution is really the
给定y 0到YT，联合分布实际上是QT的后验，所以
Joint Distribution is really the posterior of QT given y 0 to Y T so
posterior of QT given y 0 to Y T so silly the tutoring distribution it
愚蠢的补习分配实际上并没有在一天结束时
silly the tutoring distribution it doesn't really at the end of the day you
doesn't really at the end of the day you will notice any book reviews or any
完成此操作后，您会注意到任何书评或您引用的任何论文
will notice any book reviews or any papers you refer when they complete this
papers you refer when they complete this a lot of times necessary not equal they
很多时候有必要不平等，他们寻求成比例的权利，所以无论
a lot of times necessary not equal they seek proportional right so whatever the
seek proportional right so whatever the clinician you use for this if it is
您用于此的临床医生，如果它等于与i成正比的i4
clinician you use for this if it is equal to i4 proportional to alpha you
equal to i4 proportional to alpha you get the same equation so that should not
得到相同的等式，所以这不应该成为问题，所以让我给你，让我
get the same equation so that should not be an issue so let me give you let me
be an issue so let me give you let me give you B a question that we will
给您一个问题B，下周我们可能会看到
give you B a question that we will probably sort of see next week when we
probably sort of see next week when we discuss about hidden Markov models this
讨论有关隐马尔可夫模型的问题，这是板块-数量还可以
discuss about hidden Markov models this is the plate for this - quantity ok the
is the plate for this - quantity ok the Alpha message so the calculator time T
Alpha消息，因此您需要知道Alfred的计算器时间T加1 alpha
Alpha message so the calculator time T plus 1 alpha you require to know Alfred
plus 1 alpha you require to know Alfred time QT and so you know this is
时间QT，所以您知道这基本上是前向递归
time QT and so you know this is basically a forward recursive
basically a forward recursive calculation so you start from time 0 you
计算，因此您可以从时间0开始计算主时间t1，
calculation so you start from time 0 you can calculate the master time t1 and
can calculate the master time t1 and and you can keep going so this is
而且您可以继续前进，这就像我们看到的变化一样
and you can keep going so this is exactly like we have seen for change the
exactly like we have seen for change the difference of postulate for change we
假设变化的差异，我们没有观察模型，只有
difference of postulate for change we didn't have an observation model we only
didn't have an observation model we only had a transition model but you know what
有一个过渡模型，但您知道如果您实际采用该模型而您却不知道该怎么办
had a transition model but you know what if you actually take this and you don't
if you actually take this and you don't be together with this in principle you
原则上与这个结合在一起，您将得到与变化相同的等式，
be together with this in principle you get the same equation as for change and
get the same equation as for change and some words actually we don't want to
实际上我们不想将某些单词视为它们合并的新问题
some words actually we don't want to treat this as a new problem they merge
treat this as a new problem they merge the evolution equations the dynamics to
演化方程将动力学模型转化为观测模型，这样他们就可以
the evolution equations the dynamics to the observation model so they can
the observation model so they can recycle the questions that use for
回收用于检查的问题，但在这里很好
recycle the questions that use for checks but sort of here it's nicely
checks but sort of here it's nicely written okay because you explicitly see
写得还好，因为您明确看到了观察模型，并且
written okay because you explicitly see the the observation model and and also
the the observation model and and also of this transition probabilities from
从状态T到T的过渡概率加上1好的，所以这是
of this transition probabilities from state T to T plus 1 okay so this is the
state T to T plus 1 okay so this is the forward recursive equation for finding
寻找阿尔法的前向递归方程现在是贝塔弄乱了它
forward recursive equation for finding alpha this is now the beta messes it
alpha this is now the beta messes it comes to look like that and you notice
看起来像这样，您会注意到计算出来的，因为QT我们不需要
comes to look like that and you notice the calculated because QT we need not be
the calculated because QT we need not be the QT plus one so this is a bad word
QT加一，所以这是一个不好的单词方程式，当您经常
the QT plus one so this is a bad word equation and when you have made often
equation and when you have made often bit at a given time by using that both
通过使用向前和向后消息在给定的时间位
bit at a given time by using that both forward and backward messages
forward and backward messages effectively you can calculate this
有效地，您可以计算出给定的所有QT的移动分布
effectively you can calculate this moving distribution of QT given all the
moving distribution of QT given all the data from y 0 to Y T by multiplying the
通过乘以从左到右的消息，将数据从y 0到YT
data from y 0 to Y T by multiplying the messages that arrived from left and
messages that arrived from left and right at up to know the time T the
直到知道铝的时间T，我们进行消息传递时，
right at up to know the time T the aluminum we did message-passing having a
aluminum we did message-passing having a 5 marginal right you take the messages
5边缘权利，您可以接收未知的邮件，然后乘以
5 marginal right you take the messages that arrive in unknown and you multiply
that arrive in unknown and you multiply them so it's not surprising that shear
他们，所以毫不奇怪，所以我们得到相同的关系，所以这个你
them so it's not surprising that shear so we get the same relation so this you
so we get the same relation so this you know there is no Junction Ravens no
知道没有交界乌鸦，没有，你可以得出这个，你知道
know there is no Junction Ravens no nothing you can derive this you know
nothing you can derive this you know using conditional dependence relation so
使用条件依赖关系，这样您就可以推导所有
using conditional dependence relation so everything you just can deriving the
everything you just can deriving the pantograph
受电弓，所以下周我们将正式推导
pantograph so next week we will formally derive
so next week we will formally derive this using message passing algorithm
这个使用消息传递算法的沙
this using message passing algorithm sand
sand and the fact of the office and things
以及办公室之类的事实，但今天我想去
and the fact of the office and things like that but today I want to go rather
like that but today I want to go rather extreme and try to somehow we derive
极端，并尝试以某种方式使用结点3算法得出此结果，因此我们
extreme and try to somehow we derive this with the junction 3 algorithm so we
this with the junction 3 algorithm so we can just live the junction tree
可以活在我们身后的结点树算法好吧，因为是你
can just live the junction tree algorithm behind us ok because it's you
algorithm behind us ok because it's you know it's a complicated topic it's it's
知道这是一个复杂的话题，最好掩盖它
know it's a complicated topic it's it's much better to have it to cover it
much better to have it to cover it earlier on today I'm going to give you
今天早些时候，我将给您另一个块力算法，
earlier on today I'm going to give you another block force algorithm that
another block force algorithm that somehow if you don't see often in in you
以某种方式，如果您不经常看到您在参考文献中知道的内容，但我们会看到
somehow if you don't see often in in you know in references but we will see
know in references but we will see somehow that it's natural backwards
不知何故，基本上整个时期都是自然的倒退
somehow that it's natural backwards approach basically to whole period
approach basically to whole period actually done the beta messages and
实际完成了beta消息，这些就是我们所说的占主导地位的消息
actually done the beta messages and these are what we call the dominant
these are what we call the dominant cities so there are no messages so this
城市，因此没有任何消息，因此这是在所有
cities so there are no messages so this is the probability of QT given all the
is the probability of QT given all the data y0 y1 to write it ok so hopefully I
数据y0 y1可以将其正确写入，所以希望我正确正确地写入了该数据，所以现在我
data y0 y1 to write it ok so hopefully I wrote this correctly right ok so now I
wrote this correctly right ok so now I need to know why is this a backwards
如果您做对了代数，就需要知道为什么这是一个向后的信息
need to know why is this a backwards message well if you do the algebra right
message well if you do the algebra right and nothing else for conditional
对于有条件的独立关系没有别的，你可以看到
and nothing else for conditional independence relations you can see that
independence relations you can see that this one of grammar sweetie don't their
这个语法亲爱的人，不要把他们的注意力放在分母上
this one of grammar sweetie don't their attention to the denominator is really a
attention to the denominator is really a normalizing factor but it involves the
归一化因子，但是它涉及到家庭，它涉及到
normalizing factor but it involves the family it involves the calculation of
family it involves the calculation of the Alpha message which remember it's
记住它的Alpha消息是好的，但是涉及到以下功能
the Alpha message which remember it's for good but involves function of
for good but involves function of anomalous is that this computer time T
异常是这台计算机的时间为T加1，以便能够计算出伽马
anomalous is that this computer time T plus 1 so to be able to calculate gamma
plus 1 so to be able to calculate gamma time DT at time T you need start
在时间T的时间DT，您需要从链的末尾开始倒退，但
time DT at time T you need start backwards from the end of the chain but
backwards from the end of the chain but you need also to do the first
您还需要执行第一步开发以计算Alpha
you need also to do the first development step to calculate the Alpha
development step to calculate the Alpha message right so you work forward you
正确的消息，以便您继续前进，完成Alpha关系，然后
message right so you work forward you finish with the Alpha relation and then
finish with the Alpha relation and then once you have those you can start going
一旦有了这些，就可以从色域开始向后退
once you have those you can start going backwards starting with the gamut
backwards starting with the gamut to capital P and then keep updating this
到大写字母P，然后继续更新，因为您向后走好了，并且有一个
to capital P and then keep updating this as you go backwards okay and there is a
as you go backwards okay and there is a boundary condition of course at time
当然是时间资本T的边界条件，所以您可以使它工作正常
boundary condition of course at time capital T so you can so this works okay
capital T so you can so this works okay and don't need to give you this so let's
不需要给你这个，所以让我们看一下连接树
and don't need to give you this so let's look at the junction tree in exactly
look at the junction tree in exactly what the junction tree algorithm is
联结树算法将为我们做什么
what the junction tree algorithm is going to do for us
记住在结点树中，我们必须放到最大派系中
remember in the junction tree we have to put we have to find the maximal cliques
put we have to find the maximal cliques and you notice here the maximal cliques
并且您注意到这里最大的集团涉及到知识来点击其他人
and you notice here the maximal cliques involve to knowledge others that click
involve to knowledge others that click here to see what you want you want you
在这里看到你想要的东西，你想等等，我有这个点击
here to see what you want you want you to etcetera this I have this clicks so
to etcetera this I have this clicks so this potential while chopping the
这个电位同时将电位补偿q1 q2斩波为
this potential while chopping the potential subside q1 q2 is the
potential subside q1 q2 is the probability of T 2 given Q on this the
给定Q的T 2的概率于此，给定0的q1的概率为：
probability of T 2 given Q on this the probability of q1 given to 0 these are
probability of q1 given to 0 these are my transition probabilities this is high
我的过渡概率是整个领域的高潜力，然后我们
my transition probabilities this is high potentials across the tain and then we
potentials across the tain and then we have the observation clicks that involve
具有涉及Q 1 y 1 y 2 y 2的观察点击，这将是
have the observation clicks that involve Q 1 y 1 y 2 y 2 and this will be
Q 1 y 1 y 2 y 2 and this will be observation clicks alright so this for
观察点击很好，例如，这是给定y 1的概率
observation clicks alright so this for example is the probability of y 1 given
example is the probability of y 1 given 2 our probability of Y 2 given T 2 etc
2在给定T 2等的情况下，我们的Y 2的概率，我们将其取为时间资本T in
2 our probability of Y 2 given T 2 etc and we take this up to time capital T in
and we take this up to time capital T in a suppose at time 0 you want because you
假设您想要在时间0处，因为您想将其设为3，这样我们就可以
a suppose at time 0 you want because you want to make this a 3 right so we can
want to make this a 3 right so we can define this to be the probability of to
将其定义为y的观测值y 0的概率为0
define this to be the probability of to 0 times the observation of y 0 given to
0 times the observation of y 0 given to 0 so really this is the Joint
0所以这真的是Q 0 y 0的联合分布
0 so really this is the Joint Distribution of Q 0 y 0 you see that I
Distribution of Q 0 y 0 you see that I mean a time 0 right I'm gonna have I'm
意思是时间0对，我要开始，我要采样到0
mean a time 0 right I'm gonna have I'm going to start I'm going to sample to 0
going to start I'm going to sample to 0 from the initial distribution P of Q 0
从Q 0的初始分布P开始，然后赋予0，那么我要
from the initial distribution P of Q 0 and then given to 0 then I'm going to
and then given to 0 then I'm going to say what's the probability of y 0 given
说y 0赋予0的概率是多少，所以我将这两件事放在一起
say what's the probability of y 0 given to 0 so I put the two things together
to 0 so I put the two things together and I define them as this potential okay
我把它们定义为这种潜在的好处，只是为了使事情变得容易，所以我的交界处
and I define them as this potential okay just to make things easy so my junction
just to make things easy so my junction 3 loops I gotten and what you also see
我得到了3个循环，您还看到的是在这里可以看到的分隔符
3 loops I gotten and what you also see is the separators that you can see here
is the separators that you can see here these two nodes and one thing in common
这两个节点和一个共同点是0这两个知识得到
these two nodes and one thing in common which is to 0 these two knowledge get
which is to 0 these two knowledge get one thing in common which is Q 1 so I
一个共同点是Q 1，所以我给了很多不同的希腊符号
one thing in common which is Q 1 so I give different a lots of Greek symbols
give different a lots of Greek symbols here if you can pronounce them from
在这里，如果您可以说出它们的意思，您将获得额外的奖励积分
here if you can pronounce them from you're gonna get an extra bonus point in
you're gonna get an extra bonus point in your homework by Subic okay so this is
苏比克（Subic）的功课还好，所以这又是关于Q等的Q对P的问题
your homework by Subic okay so this is again Q to P of Q on etcetera
因此，我们通过这种潜力介绍这些权利是这些过渡
so so we introduce this right through this potentials are these transition
this potentials are these transition probabilities these are the observation
这些概率都是观察模型，所以我们初始化所有
probabilities these are the observation models all right so we initialize all
models all right so we initialize all the potentials to one right so we start
潜能正确，所以我们开始将所有潜能都称为
the potentials to one right so we start we put every potential to be called
we put every potential to be called every separator to be the potential
每个可能的分隔符都等于1我必须等待
every separator to be the potential survives be equal to 1 I have to wait to
survives be equal to 1 I have to wait to know what its life has right but don't
知道自己的生活是对的，但不要阅读，我们将对此进行解释
know what its life has right but don't read this and we will explain this
read this and we will explain this graphically ok ok
以图形方式可以从集团50 YP确定，所以也许可以这样
graphically ok ok from the clique 50 YP so maybe from this
from the clique 50 YP so maybe from this click here to - ok
单击此处-再次确定，我们收到相同的消息
click here to - ok again we are getting the same messages
again we are getting the same messages from this clicked up to this trick so
从这个点击到这个技巧，所以请记住当您提供正确的服务时，
from this clicked up to this trick so remember when you services are right you
remember when you services are right you are going to have to update the
将不得不更新分隔符，然后一旦你采​​取
are going to have to update the separator and then once you have take
separator and then once you have take the separator then you have to abate the
分隔符，那么您就必须减少电位键的作用
the separator then you have to abate the potential side to one key to the
potential side to one key to the election but right now I'm going to take
选举，但现在我要接受从这里传播的所有消息
election but right now I'm going to take messages propagating from here up all
messages propagating from here up all the way so from side petrol right to
从右边的汽油一直到消沉的方式-阿姨-好的，你能告诉我吗
the way so from side petrol right to subside - auntie - alright can you tell
subside - auntie - alright can you tell me traumatically right so we don't need
我很受创伤，所以我们不需要基于联结树的问题
me traumatically right so we don't need the questions based on the junction tree
the questions based on the junction tree algorithm so we start with one what is
算法，所以我们从一个开始，什么是新的分隔器电位，即
algorithm so we start with one what is the new separator potential which is a
the new separator potential which is a function of t2
t2的功能
我在计算机上看到了类似的东西，您知道那是什么，然后我去了
the new separator potential which is a function of t2
I see something on the computers like that you know it was like and I went to
我在计算机上看到了类似的东西，您知道那是什么，然后我去了
that you know it was like and I went to some high place they don't like myself
他们不喜欢自己的杯子的高处，你知道吗，所以一定是一些东西
some high place they don't like myself cup you know right so must be something
cup you know right so must be something like that everything is in the computer
就像一切都在电脑里一样，所以这就是为什么我不会
like that everything is in the computer all right so that's why I'm not gonna be
all right so that's why I'm not gonna be posting anything anymore you know it's
发布任何东西，你知道这太累了，试试这血，那是什么
posting anything anymore you know it's too tiring try this blood so what is
too tiring try this blood so what is that benefit separate the potential you
好处将您记住的潜力分离出来，找到了更新后的潜力
that benefit separate the potential you remember to find the updated potential
remember to find the updated potential maybe we have to do this potential here
也许我们必须在这里发挥这种潜力，我们已经整合了什么
maybe we have to do this potential here we have integrated with respect to what
we have integrated with respect to what variable at this point okay okay because
变量在这一点上好吧好吧，因为显然与连接树完全一样
variable at this point okay okay because clearly with exactly the junction tree
clearly with exactly the junction tree algorithm knows best
算法知道得最好，所以我们不正确，所以你告诉
algorithm knows best so we don't otherwise right so you tell
so we don't otherwise right so you tell me when I integrate this with respect to
当我将其相对于Y进行积分以更改相对值并告诉我时
me when I integrate this with respect to Y to change the relative and tell me
Y to change the relative and tell me what that will give you
那会给你什么
因此，当我整合这种潜力时，我们发现这种潜力就是尊重
Y to change the relative and tell me what that will give you
so when I integrate this potential we discover this potential is to respect to
因此，当我整合这种潜力时，我们发现这种潜力就是尊重
discover this potential is to respect to Y 2
Y 2 Z星是什么
Y 2 what will the Z star be what is this
what will the Z star be what is this potential
潜在的
您必须重新考虑我们原来的问题吧
what will the Z star be what is this potential
you have to think again our original problem right
您必须重新考虑我们原来的问题吧
problem right what is that potential here here I can
这里的潜力是什么，我可以说是你的国王，所以当你
what is that potential here here I can say is it's the king of you so when you
say is it's the king of you so when you named the greatest returns with respect
就巴里·马昂（Bhari maang）的成就命名为最大回报
named the greatest returns with respect to what bhari maang
to what bhari maang we said why son I'll observe right now
我们说了为什么儿子我现在要观察，所以有多少钱
we said why son I'll observe right now so with respect to how much is that so
so with respect to how much is that so the separation potential then will not
那么分离的潜力就不会改变。
the separation potential then will not change all right how about this
change all right how about this potential here so the message now from
潜力在这里，所以来自最高级的信息现在在那里
potential here so the message now from the superlative was in there
the superlative was in there so we have made this form of this
因此，我们已经将这种形式的这种潜力变为可能
so we have made this form of this potential will be there is a potential
potential will be there is a potential times we have delegates of electric
时代我们有代表的电势除以原始
times we have delegates of electric potential divided by the original
potential divided by the original potential separator potential which is
电位分离器的电位是相对运动，所以这个电位
potential separator potential which is relative motion so this potential we
relative motion so this potential we should not say so when messages with
当有智慧的讯息被观察时，不应该这样说。
should not say so when messages with wise being an observed when messages are
wise being an observed when messages are sent from this critics upwards the this
从这个评论家那里向上发送的q0 q1 q1 q2的这种潜在的叹息等等
sent from this critics upwards the this potential sigh of q0 q1 q1 q2 etc do not
potential sigh of q0 q1 q1 q2 etc do not change so the junction tree algorithm
进行更改，以使结点树算法无法执行任何操作，所以让我们来看一下
change so the junction tree algorithm does nothing ok all right so let's see
does nothing ok all right so let's see [Applause]
[鼓掌]现在让我们做以下事情
[Applause] so now let's do the following thing
so now let's do the following thing let's send messages from from k0 y 0 to
让我们从k0 y 0到p 0发送消息qm消息hmm，所以我们将
let's send messages from from k0 y 0 to p 0 qm messages hmm so we're going to
p 0 qm messages hmm so we're going to send messages from here to there from
从这里到那里，当然也从这里，发送消息
send messages from here to there from there to there and of course from here
there to there and of course from here to there so if this message what is so
到那里，如果这条消息是最好的，那就去发送消息
to there so if this message what is so best to make is going to send messages
best to make is going to send messages to this plea can you tell me what is the
您能否告诉我P星的客观价值是多少
to this plea can you tell me what is the objective value is going to be of P star
objective value is going to be of P star to 0
到0
使用算法的主要思想开始计算鱼的新值
objective value is going to be of P star to 0
using the main idea of the algorithm start to calculate the new value fish
使用算法的主要思想开始计算鱼的新值
start to calculate the new value fish this time to zero what do we have to do
这次归零，我们对此尊敬的潜在面试该怎么做
this time to zero what do we have to do to this potential interview with respect
to this potential interview with respect my body my body will do zero so remember
我的身体我的身体将为零，所以请记住他告诉我的这种潜力，那就是
my body my body will do zero so remember this potential he had told me it was the
this potential he had told me it was the joint distribution of Q zero Y zero
Q零Y的联合分布请记住，因为它包含了它
joint distribution of Q zero Y zero remember because it included the it
remember because it included the it included the prior of K 0 and also the
包括K 0的先验和y 0到0的观测值，因为我们知道
included the prior of K 0 and also the observation of y 0 into 0 since we know
observation of y 0 into 0 since we know joint okay Broadway so the reason
百老汇联合还好吧，原因可能与联合圈有关
joint okay Broadway so the reason potentially with the joint circle
potentially with the joint circle integrative respect to y 0 you get P of
相对于y 0的综合方面，您得到Q 0的P，因此立即您可以看到
integrative respect to y 0 you get P of Q 0 so immediately you can see that this
Q 0 so immediately you can see that this peak potential becomes a marginal so
峰值电势变得微不足道，所以突然有意思了
peak potential becomes a marginal so suddenly has a meaning it's nothing else
suddenly has a meaning it's nothing else but the marginal of to 0 so let's see
但边际为0，所以让我们看看发生了什么事，道具过时了
but the marginal of to 0 so let's see what's going to happen the prop dated we
what's going to happen the prop dated we will take the or potential which is the
将采用或电位，即您被赋予0的概率，而这
will take the or potential which is the probability you are given to 0 and this
probability you are given to 0 and this we told is the marginal so this this
我们说的是边际，所以这个产品是进行QR的联合，所以
we told is the marginal so this this product is the joint of proceeding QR so
product is the joint of proceeding QR so the clinic potentials now become
现在诊所的潜力变得微不足道了，所以也许我应该打电话给
the clinic potentials now become marginal social so maybe I should call
marginal social so maybe I should call this potential now becomes 2 marginally
这个潜力现在变成2也许这成为当我们记住的时候
this potential now becomes 2 marginally maybe this becomes a remember when we
maybe this becomes a remember when we said that the joint probability
说联合概率分布是
said that the joint probability distribution is the product of the
distribution is the product of the maximal clique potentials divided by the
您可以实际看到最大的集团势除以分隔符吗
maximal clique potentials divided by the separators can you actually visualize
separators can you actually visualize now about what because it first becomes
现在关于什么，因为它首先变成了边缘，所以另一个变成了
now about what because it first becomes this marginal so the other one to become
this marginal so the other one to become the submariners maybe that works really
潜艇也许真的很好，你们可以做代数，
the submariners maybe that works really okay and you can guys do the algebra and
okay and you can guys do the algebra and you can see that which works fine
您可以看到效果很好
因此，当您从这里向那里发送消息，然后从那里向
okay and you can guys do the algebra and you can see that which works fine
so when you send message from here to there alright and and from there to
因此，当您从这里向那里发送消息，然后从那里向
there alright and and from there to there okay
好的，这变成了边缘，我
there okay well this becomes this marginal and I
well this becomes this marginal and I remind you the message from here upwards
提醒您从此处向上传递的消息不适合，因此现在我们需要
remind you the message from here upwards does not fit so now what we will need to
does not fit so now what we will need to do is we will need to send the message
要做的是，我们需要将消息从此处发送到点击Q 1年，因此
do is we will need to send the message from here down to the click Q 1 yr so
from here down to the click Q 1 yr so you have to tell me what is the new
您必须告诉我，它了解新的变体是什么
you have to tell me what is the new variant does it understand of going to
variant does it understand of going to be sure it is the degree of this no
当消息来自时，请确保这是没有潜力的程度
be sure it is the degree of this no potential when the message comes from
potential when the message comes from here and it's going down so how do I
在这里，它正在下降，所以我怎么计算这个员工，它会永远停止吗
here and it's going down so how do I calculate this staff does it ever stop
calculate this staff does it ever stop now
现在[音乐]
now [Music]
并告诉我，该潜在列表为Q 0 Q 1的P，所以0 0为
with respect and tell me that this potential list is P of Q 0 Q 1 so 0 0 of
potential list is P of Q 0 Q 1 so 0 0 of acumen becomes what becomes a 0 now do
敏锐变成0现在你说变成纯P是指这个
acumen becomes what becomes a 0 now do you say becomes P of pure refers to this
you say becomes P of pure refers to this potential originally because you never
最初的潜力，因为您从不改变如果您扭转了
potential originally because you never changed what if you reverse the
changed what if you reverse the probability of y 1 given Q 1 x now the
在给定Q 1 x的情况下y 1的概率现在将开始的新势Z
probability of y 1 given Q 1 x now the new potential Z that will start and we
new potential Z that will start and we told me was what B if you are divided by
告诉我，如果您将B除以1，那么B是什么，所以新的电势将是
told me was what B if you are divided by 1 so the new potential is going to be
1 so the new potential is going to be what now
现在怎么办
很容易是纯白人女性q1然后乘以P
1 so the new potential is going to be what now
so easily it was pure white women q1 and then you multiplied by P a few ones so
很容易是纯白人女性q1然后乘以P
then you multiplied by P a few ones so that gives you a circle of why you want
这给了您一个为什么要圈的信息，这样您现在就可以看到，即使您
that gives you a circle of why you want so you can see now that even this you
so you can see now that even this you know potentials also become marginal so
知道电位也变得微不足道，所以高兴的只有峰值电位
know potentials also become marginal so happy the only the peak potentials
happy the only the peak potentials become arsenals and then effectively the
成为武库，然后有效地使分隔符变成她的边缘，甚至
become arsenals and then effectively the separators becomes her marginal or even
separators becomes her marginal or even you may say what's going on where is the
您可能会说发生了什么事，另一个消息在哪里，更大的消息在哪里？
you may say what's going on where is the other message where's the bigger message
other message where's the bigger message I'm confused right so okay so let's see
我很困惑，没关系，所以让我们看看，这仅是原理图
I'm confused right so okay so let's see so this is just a schematic again of the
so this is just a schematic again of the what the other if like we presented
如果像我们介绍的那样，另一个又如何呢？所以我们开始从发送消息
what the other if like we presented right so we start sending messages from
right so we start sending messages from these clips by just completing the
只需完成分隔符，然后使用此剪辑即可
these clips by just completing the separators all right and then using this
separators all right and then using this product which we've updated separator
我们已经更新了分离器电位除以原件的产品
product which we've updated separator potential divided by the originals we
potential divided by the originals we update this Creek potential and the only
更新此Creek的潜力，以及此示意图上唯一的区别是
update this Creek potential and the only difference on this schematic from what
difference on this schematic from what we had before here this node has
我们之前在此节点上有多个子节点，因此我们采取了
we had before here this node has multiple children so we have taken
multiple children so we have taken further the same way we do with message
进一步地，我们与传递消息的方式相同，然后在相反的步骤中，
further the same way we do with message passing and then on the reverse step we
passing and then on the reverse step we distribute the information from this
将信息从该节点分发给子节点，因此我们应用了
distribute the information from this node to the children so we applied the
node to the children so we applied the separators alright so we calculate the
好的分隔符，所以我们以之前和之前的方式计算分隔符
separators alright so we calculate the separators the way we did before and
separators the way we did before and then we multiplied with the double style
然后我们用双重风格相乘，我们试图更新潜力
then we multiplied with the double style which we trying to update the potentials
which we trying to update the potentials of this now right that's what we did
现在，这就是我们所做的
好的
which we trying to update the potentials of this now right that's what we did
okay
您知道的没错，因此请考虑一下，以便可以将其表示为定义明确的
you know right so think of this so this can be represented as a well-defined
can be represented as a well-defined table okay so the difference because
桌子好吧，所以区别是因为给定的这个y星是我要带的
table okay so the difference because this y star given is I am going to take
this y star given is I am going to take these two positive potentials to be the
如果给定50，这两个正电位是YT的条件，所以如果我看
these two positive potentials to be the conditional of YT given 50 so if I look
conditional of YT given 50 so if I look here I'm going to fake this to start
在这里我要假装的是从给定Q到y2的条件开始的
here I'm going to fake this to start with that is the condition of y2 given Q
with that is the condition of y2 given Q - okay in case you know you know you can
-好吧，如果您知道您知道可以解决这个问题，
- okay in case you know you know you can come up to this you know with
come up to this you know with forgiveness but let's say I am going to
宽恕，但假设我要使用分隔电位作为
forgiveness but let's say I am going to use the separator potential to be the
use the separator potential to be the probability of YJ given kitty
幸运的是，给定小猫咪的YJ概率，阿尔法发生了什么
probability of YJ given kitty fortunately what happens to the alpha
fortunately what happens to the alpha messages to the bigger messages etc
信息传递给更大的信息，等等，让我们找出投资者
messages to the bigger messages etc let's figure out investors that is
let's figure out investors that is propagating in this case flow from here
在这种情况下，传播从这里流向此单击，然后向下
propagating in this case flow from here to this click alright and then down
to this click alright and then down there so how to update using the
在那里，如何使用连接树算法更新此关节
there so how to update using the junction tree algorithm this joint
junction tree algorithm this joint potential of 50 and 50 plus one
50和50加1的潜力，所以记住消息将是
potential of 50 and 50 plus one so remember messages are going to be
so remember messages are going to be coming from this separator and they're
来自这个分离器，他们将来自这个分离器，
coming from this separator and they're gonna be coming from this separator and
gonna be coming from this separator and we are actually start with that this
我们实际上是从这个消息来自分隔符开始的
we are actually start with that this message is coming from the separators
message is coming from the separators have no all right because my name is
没有任何权利，因为我的名字叫拉克尔（Raquel），所以我们必须开始
have no all right because my name is Raquel should be so we have to start you
Raquel should be so we have to start you know with this messages from the leeches
知道了这些来自水ches的消息，让我们说它们是已知的，我们想要
know with this messages from the leeches let's say that they're known and we want
let's say that they're known and we want to update this potential emotion we want
更新这种潜在的情感，我们想在那里更新这种操作者的潜力
to update this potential emotion we want to update this operator potential there
to update this operator potential there so this operator sends a message and we
因此，该操作员发送了一条消息，我们希望了解这种潜在的变化
so this operator sends a message and we want to see how this potential changes
want to see how this potential changes so look at this equation the first line
所以在第一行看这个方程式，告诉我这可能是
so look at this equation the first line and told me it could be the junction to
and told me it could be the junction to algorithm members mistake
算法成员错误
我们应该是这个潜力的新潜力
and told me it could be the junction to algorithm members mistake
what we're supposed to be the new potential of this potential the new
我们应该是这个潜力的新潜力
potential of this potential the new potential supposed to be the new
潜力应该是新的潜力，这是
potential supposed to be the new potential which is this times the
potential which is this times the product of the Feist and demanded money
Feist的产品和原本要求的钱我们和原先的三个
product of the Feist and demanded money originally we and the original three
originally we and the original three senses we take them equal to 1 so the
感觉我们取它们等于1，所以这里的乘积就是
senses we take them equal to 1 so the show the product here will be of this
show the product here will be of this part of QT and the product of this part
QT的一部分和QT加1的乘积，我告诉你
part of QT and the product of this part of QT plus 1 and I told you that there
of QT plus 1 and I told you that there takes the start of KP plus 1 to make the
以KP的开始加1来计算YT的概率加给定QT的加1
takes the start of KP plus 1 to make the probability of YT plus 1 given QT plus 1
probability of YT plus 1 given QT plus 1 so basically the only thing that I am
所以基本上我在这里唯一没有字面意义上的分歧
so basically the only thing that I am this here that doesn't literally divide
this here that doesn't literally divide right something from the separated
从k加1的分离势中得到一些东西
right something from the separated potential from k plus 1 ways by
potential from k plus 1 ways by marginalizing this potential because
边缘化这种潜力，因为成员的点击潜力不是
marginalizing this potential because this click potential the members is not
this click potential the members is not a distribution as environment variables
作为环境变量的分布，因为我们一直观察到
a distribution as environment variables because we always observed so in
because we always observed so in principle I am using this by calculating
原则上，我是根据以前的情况计算出来的
principle I am using this by calculating from the case that we had before where
from the case that we had before where this thing was the new potential child
这件事是新的潜在孩子是或潜在时间P星的时间
this thing was the new potential child is the or potential times P star times
is the or potential times P star times the separator potential Z star so this
分离器潜在的Z星，所以这是我的过渡模型，这是
the separator potential Z star so this is my transition model this is this
is my transition model this is this power of U star and this is my
U星的力量，这是我的观测模型，让我们计算一下
power of U star and this is my observation model and let's calculate
observation model and let's calculate now so this is the new update can give
现在，这是新的更新，可以给出一个问题来计算这次50
now so this is the new update can give in a question to calculate this time 50
in a question to calculate this time 50 plus 1 what would be so we were moving
加1会是什么，所以我们在链上向前迈进了
plus 1 what would be so we were moving forward on the chain what will be the
forward on the chain what will be the new simulator potential fist R of Q T
QT的新模拟器潜在拳头R加1
new simulator potential fist R of Q T plus 1
plus 1 what's my definition of calculating you
我对计算的定义是什么，您知道他们的前一页
what's my definition of calculating you know the forward a page of them of the
know the forward a page of them of the separator potential when we need to come
需要计算这种TP时需要的分离器电位
separator potential when we need to come to do to calculate this kind of TP plus
to do to calculate this kind of TP plus one we need to start with what potential
我们需要从什么潜力开始
请记住，如果我们有严格的潜力，晶体是计算出来的，
to do to calculate this kind of TP plus one we need to start with what potential
remember the crystals are calculated if we have strictly potential and the
请记住，如果我们有严格的潜力，晶体是计算出来的，
we have strictly potential and the message propagate right to the separator
消息直接传播到分隔符，我们在技术上最终可能会采用这种方式
message propagate right to the separator we technically potential finally the way
we technically potential finally the way the various materials from the separator
分离器中的各种材料，以便您利用我们的潜力
the various materials from the separator so that potential do you take we take
so that potential do you take we take the Tristar QT QT plus 1 that was just a
Tristar QT QT加1只是毯子，这就是我们的潜力
the Tristar QT QT plus 1 that was just a blanket this is the potential we just
blanket this is the potential we just have a few things here so we're going to
这里有几件事，所以我们要采用这一点，我们将进行整合
have a few things here so we're going to take this and we're going to integrate
take this and we're going to integrate what kind of allowed completely all
哪种允许完全没关系，所以定义水晶50加1
what kind of allowed completely all right so to define crystal 50 plus 1
right so to define crystal 50 plus 1 we're going to have this size star of QT
我们将拥有这个QT QT的大小星星加1，这是来自
we're going to have this size star of QT QT plus 1 which is this expression from
QT plus 1 which is this expression from the slide before and we're going to
幻灯片，如果您确信，我们将把它与QT集成
the slide before and we're going to integrate this with QT if you convinced
integrate this with QT if you convinced you know what the Alpha mess is at 50
您知道50加1时的Alpha混乱是什么，这就是Alpha混乱了
you know what the Alpha mess is at 50 plus 1 and this is the Alpha messed up
plus 1 and this is the Alpha messed up UT this equation is identical the
UT这个方程与您用
UT this equation is identical the equation that you derived with the
equation that you derived with the conditional independence relations that
我之前给你的条件独立关系
conditional independence relations that I gave you earlier
I gave you earlier so the junction tree hug with basically
所以结点树的拥抱基本上发现了一个著名的递归
so the junction tree hug with basically discovered a well-known recursive
discovered a well-known recursive equation for updating the correlations
用来更新相关性的等式
equation for updating the correlations okay
这对我来说非常好，这是最好的例子
and it is sort of a very nice I mean to me that's the best example to
me that's the best example to demonstrate how the junction tree
展示联结树算法的工作原理，因为它为您提供了
demonstrate how the junction tree algorithm works because it gives you an
algorithm works because it gives you an answer that
回答您知道这并不明显，但您会
answer that you know it is not obvious but you will
you know it is not obvious but you will get it but you know but if you don't
知道了，但您知道，但是如果您没有，那就知道有问题
get it but you know but if you don't have it you know that there's a problem
have it you know that there's a problem so this is a welcome basically proof of
因此，这基本上是一个令人欢迎的一致性和工作能力的证明。
so this is a welcome basically proof of consistency and the working ability of
consistency and the working ability of the or reduction tree algorithm ok so
或归约树算法确定，所以这是Alpha消息，因此，当
the or reduction tree algorithm ok so this is the alpha message and so when
this is the alpha message and so when you propagate the message is all the way
您将消息一直传播到您知道的投票位置
you propagate the message is all the way to the you know to the location you vote
to the you know to the location you vote from the leaves all the way to the root
如果您计算的话，从树叶一直到根部一直到根部
from the leaves all the way to the root at the end of the day if you calculate
at the end of the day if you calculate the updated the final updating potential
更新后的最终更新潜力您的三明治在这里是Q的大小部分
the updated the final updating potential your sandwich here the size part of Q
your sandwich here the size part of Q capital P and Q capital t minus 1 all
大写字母P和Q大写字母t减去1好吧，这是我使用的方程式
capital P and Q capital t minus 1 all right this is I am using the equation we
right this is I am using the equation we had on the previous slide when I apply
在上一张幻灯片中，当我有效地将其应用于根时，您可以
had on the previous slide when I apply this to the root effectively you can
this to the root effectively you can show that this gives you the joint
证明这给了你y 0到y资本T的联合分布
show that this gives you the joint distribution of y 0 to y capital T and
distribution of y 0 to y capital T and QT minus 1 to P P so actually when you
QT减1到PP，所以实际上当您将这两个变量整合到一起时
QT minus 1 to P P so actually when you integrate these two variables out on
integrate these two variables out on this final update of size star you can
这颗恒星的最后更新，您可以获得前锋的边际能力
this final update of size star you can get the marginal aptitude with a forward
get the marginal aptitude with a forward calculation ok
好的计算就可以了
calculation ok so effectively the calculation of the
so effectively the calculation of the marginal likelihood from the calculation
计算使它们变得明显复杂的边际可能性
marginal likelihood from the calculation that takes them to apparent complexity
that takes them to apparent complexity now it becomes something much easier
现在变得更容易了，因为您只需要集成两个
now it becomes something much easier because you only have to integrate two
because you only have to integrate two variables with the assumption of course
当然假设可以计算此Alpha消息的变量
variables with the assumption of course that this alpha messages can be computed
that this alpha messages can be computed recursively
从出现的这个方程递归
recursively from this equation at which appear
from this equation at which appear that's basically you know there are
基本上，您知道这里的K乘以K
that's basically you know there are multiplications here of this K by K
multiplications here of this K by K matrix with a k-dimensional vector so
具有k维向量的矩阵，所以它的复杂度是所有​​元素的平衡
matrix with a k-dimensional vector so the complexity of this is balance of all
the complexity of this is balance of all basically right
基本上正确，您知道它并不太复杂，所以
basically right you know it's not too complicated so
you know it's not too complicated so this correlation was not going backwards
这种相关性不会倒退，有人可以帮我说一下，当我们得到
this correlation was not going backwards can somebody help me to say when we get
can somebody help me to say when we get the beta messages or we get this wheel
beta消息，否则我们会患上车轮疾病，但通常您不会
the beta messages or we get this wheel dominus disease but usually you don't
dominus disease but usually you don't see them when you talk about
当你谈论他们时，看到他们
好吧，因为所以我们需要点双星猫，你能帮我吗
dominus disease but usually you don't see them when you talk about
okay because so we need to point t double star of kitty can you help me on
好吧，因为所以我们需要点双星猫，你能帮我吗
double star of kitty can you help me on how the population may look like just so
人口看起来如何，所以您知道记得更新一下，如果
how the population may look like just so you know remember to update you know if
you know remember to update you know if you have this separate the right and
你有权利和力量学期的权利，所以
you have this separate the right and strength semesters right so the
strength semesters right so the potentials basically would be the
势基本上就是原始势x除以T星
potentials basically would be the original potentials x divided by T star
original potentials x divided by T star all right and then when you integrate
好的，然后当您将所有内容实际上从
all right and then when you integrate everything out apparently actually from
everything out apparently actually from this message that comes from below when
当您整合到茶中时，来自下面的此消息将使您能够
this message that comes from below when you integrate out to tea you'll be able
you integrate out to tea you'll be able to get switched double style 50 so what
要切换双样式50，那我该怎么写
to get switched double style 50 so what should I write
预期这是我们同意的吗
in anticipation does this we agree on this
this the psystar novel style of QT QT + 1 is
QT QT +1的psystar小说风格是先前的潜在知识P
the psystar novel style of QT QT + 1 is the previous potential knowledge P
the previous potential knowledge P double star divided by Q prime what
双星除以Q素数以前的模型没有发生什么
double star divided by Q prime what happened to the previous model no there
happened to the previous model no there is a picture here okay so so look at
是一张图片好吗，所以看这个方程式，这是下一个传感器
is a picture here okay so so look at this equation is this the next sensor
this equation is this the next sensor you do a papist
你做一个教皇主义者，我认为我的潜能增加了
you do a papist I think the on potential I multiplied
I think the on potential I multiplied with the double star and I'm going to do
和双星一起，我将从他们做起，直到我找不到
with the double star and I'm going to do my starting from them until I won't find
my starting from them until I won't find that recursive relation for this divided
该递归关系除以原始消息3星，即
that recursive relation for this divided by the original message 3 star which was
by the original message 3 star which was my initial message we've never from the
我最初的信息是我们永远不会从正演算法中获取信息，所以这是
my initial message we've never from the forward algorithm all right so this is
forward algorithm all right so this is the potential okay now how do we get all
潜在的好吧，现在我们如何解决问题
the potential okay now how do we get all right
right so how do we get feedback we start with
那么我们如何从Kitty开始获得反馈
so how do we get feedback we start with kitty
那么什么是耗散告诉你什么
so what is dissipation tell you what
基本上我要做的是我停下来，因为从我说的是
basically what I do is I take I stop all right because from what I say this is
right because from what I say this is try start or a freestyle times P double
尝试开始或自由泳乘以P的双素数，然后整合到T加号
try start or a freestyle times P double prime and then I integrate out to T plus
prime and then I integrate out to T plus one
现在我看不到任何东西
one now I don't see anything coming from
now I don't see anything coming from below is that the we monitored nothing -
下面是我们什么都没监视-从下面
below is that the we monitored nothing - from below
在我看来，知道方程式正确无异
knowing that the equations correct seems to me nothing comes from below right
to me nothing comes from below right what you guys were going to be in in
你们将要陷入的困境
what you guys were going to be in in terrible
terrible so let's assuming that nothing comes
因此，让我们假设没有任何事情来自于此，那么发送什么
so let's assuming that nothing comes from this all right so what sending
from this all right so what sending message is so this is actually you know
消息是这样，实际上这是您知道分配步骤的含义，所以
message is so this is actually you know what this is of the distributive step so
what this is of the distributive step so the idea here is you are going to have
这里的想法是，您将拥有此消息，向您发送此消息
the idea here is you are going to have this message sending you a message this
this message sending you a message this way and a message that way so we will
方式和消息方式，以便我们对此进行更新，但会对其进行更新，
way and a message that way so we will update this we will update that but
update this we will update that but right now we're looking on the back
现在我们正在寻找背面，希望将其分布在这里
right now we're looking on the back wants to distribute there where this
wants to distribute there where this double star potential will update this
双星势将更新，这将更新，然后我们将更新
double star potential will update this will update out and then we'll update
will update out and then we'll update that this is the new message to double
这是给双星的新讯息，如果您租用它，可以明确
that this is the new message to double star and if you rent it okay explicitly
star and if you rent it okay explicitly and you crave this will double star to
而您渴望这将使双星成为真实的信息，说明您知道
and you crave this will double star to be a real message this equation that you
be a real message this equation that you get is identical to the gamma backwards
get与可以获取的gamma向后传播消息相同
get is identical to the gamma backwards propagation message that you can get
propagation message that you can get directly with conditional independence
直接与条件独立关系有关，所以这里的想法是
directly with conditional independence relations so the idea here is rather
relations so the idea here is rather than doing a forward step where you find
而不是向前迈出一步，在其中您可以找到结果的实质和伪经
than doing a forward step where you find the outcome essence and apocryphal
the outcome essence and apocryphal define the beta messages you can reform
定义可以重新设置的Beta消息，除非您定义了alpha消息
define the beta messages you can reform unless you define the alpha messages
unless you define the alpha messages change the Alpha messages and then you
更改Alpha消息，然后执行四步操作，因为我们需要
change the Alpha messages and then you do ma quad step because we need the
do ma quad step because we need the alchemist is here to update the data
炼金术士在这里更新数据消息，一旦您有一个
alchemist is here to update the data messages and once you have the a
messages and once you have the a question there are no messages you can
问题是没有消息，您基本上可以计算任何数量的
question there are no messages you can basically compute any quantity of
basically compute any quantity of interest directly so you can do the
直接感兴趣，因此您可以进行滤波，就可以知道平滑
interest directly so you can do the filtering you know the smoothing
filtering you know the smoothing distributions predictions
直接使用此未命中消息进行分布预测等
distributions predictions etc directly using this miss messages so
etc directly using this miss messages so that's how the algorithm looks basically
这就是该算法在结点树上的基本外观，同时建议
that's how the algorithm looks basically for Junction tree okay and while suggest
for Junction tree okay and while suggest us you know spend some time doing the
我们知道，我们花一些时间做答案Rob我不能写，因为我们做了
us you know spend some time doing the answer Rob I can't write because we made
answer Rob I can't write because we made the the a page a list
页面列表
实际上，我说的更近一点，我们有一个不错的情节，这确实可以做任何事情
answer Rob I can't write because we made the the a page a list
actually even closer I said we have them a nice plot this does really do anything
实际上，我说的更近一点，我们有一个不错的情节，这确实可以做任何事情
a nice plot this does really do anything you need to know alright this is the
您需要知道好吧，这是路口300好的，所以您收集
you need to know alright this is the junction 300 okay so you collect
junction 300 okay so you collect messages from the children how do you do
孩子们的来信你如何做到这一点使这种潜力边缘化
messages from the children how do you do this marginalizing this potential
this marginalizing this potential eliminating all but the bottom was
消除除底部以外的所有东西，然后将它们形成分离器
eliminating all but the bottom was involved in the separators then form the
involved in the separators then form the product of the new separators divided by
新分隔符的乘积除以旧分隔符再乘以
product of the new separators divided by the old ones multiplying with the
the old ones multiplying with the current potential you update the
当前电势，您将更新留声机的电势
current potential you update the potential that's the phonograph step
potential that's the phonograph step down and if you want meant to go
向下，如果您想倒退并将信息分发给
down and if you want meant to go backwards and distribute information to
backwards and distribute information to the children effectively what you need
孩子们有效地要做的是找到新的
the children effectively what you need to do is find a new supply of
to do is find a new supply of pretentious integrating everything out
自命不凡地整合除分隔符变量之外的所有内容，然后
pretentious integrating everything out except the separator variables and then
except the separator variables and then update basically the new potentials as
基本上像旧的一样更新新的潜力
update basically the new potentials as the old ones
the old ones times the product of the new separator
乘以新分离器电位的乘积，此P双星除以
times the product of the new separator potentials this P double star divided by
potentials this P double star divided by the previous ones and the previous ones
以前的那些和以前的那些都记得会有一个你
the previous ones and the previous ones remember there would be one that you
remember there would be one that you computed in the forward step so you can
在前进步骤中进行了计算，因此您实际上可以在这里欣赏
computed in the forward step so you can actually appreciate here for something
actually appreciate here for something you can say if this were the alpha
您可以说这是否是Alpha信息，您可以在这里看到您需要的信息
you can say if this were the alpha messages right you can see here you need
messages right you can see here you need to keep track of the other messages to
跟踪其他消息，以便能够分发
to keep track of the other messages to be able to do the distribution of
be able to do the distribution of information for fairness to the children
对儿童公平的信息
因此，这种iWitness基本上具有您所能获得的强大功能
be able to do the distribution of information for fairness to the children
so this iWitness is basically as powerful as you can get with
因此，这种iWitness基本上具有您所能获得的强大功能
powerful as you can get with probabilistic graphical models and you
概率图形模型，您知道其中有几种不同类型的
probabilistic graphical models and you know there are sort of different type of
know there are sort of different type of ways of implementing this that I think
我认为我们在演讲中强调的实现方式
ways of implementing this that I think we highlighted on the lecture on
we highlighted on the lecture on Thursday but - what you see this is what
星期四，但是-您看到的这还不错，这很好，因为在
Thursday but - what you see this is what you get okay and it's nice because in
you get okay and it's nice because in essence the algorithm is really doing
本质上，算法实际上是在树上进行推理，但是树是
essence the algorithm is really doing inference on a tree but the tree is a
inference on a tree but the tree is a tree of cliques so basically we to be
派系之树，所以基本上我们可以使用我们转变的所有这些想法
tree of cliques so basically we to be able to use all these ideas we transform
able to use all these ideas we transform the original glass right the rafter all
原来的玻璃杯就在所有right子的右边-到达一个结点树，
the original glass right the rafter all of the left--it to a junction tree which
of the left--it to a junction tree which is you know a tree basically potentials
您是否知道一棵基本上被点击的树，我们注意到当您
is you know a tree basically potentials that are clicked and we notice when you
that are clicked and we notice when you implement this algorithm basically at
至少在没有证据的情况下基本上实现该算法
implement this algorithm basically at least with no evidence the potentials
least with no evidence the potentials come to be marginals the separators come
成为边缘的分隔符成为次要的主人什么证据是一个小问题
come to be marginals the separators come to be sub master what evidence is a wee
to be sub master what evidence is a wee bit more complicated than that any
比关于联结树的任何问题都要复杂一点
bit more complicated than that any questions about the junction tree
questions about the junction tree algorithm you need to at least you know
算法，您至少需要知道，我建议您知道这一点，也许
algorithm you need to at least you know I would suggest this you know maybe take
I would suggest this you know maybe take you have not even you know the hmm
你甚至都没有，我只知道hmm mobile的同一个型号
you have not even you know the hmm mobile same model I only have leaves you
mobile same model I only have leaves you know the dynamic you know the transition
知道动态，就知道状态的转变，并应用它，看看是否
know the dynamic you know the transition of states and apply this and see if you
of states and apply this and see if you get you know the Alpha and the beta
让您完全像我们之前那样了解Alpha和Beta消息，以及
get you know the Alpha and the beta messages exactly as we did before and
messages exactly as we did before and then of course repeat these calculations
然后当然要重复这些计算，以尝试从中传播一些消息
then of course repeat these calculations try to some propagating messages from
try to some propagating messages from the leaves to the rope the root path and
叶子到绳子的根部路径，走你所得到的，看看你所得到的
the leaves to the rope the root path and take what you get and see what you get
take what you get and see what you get is what's listed in the book
136正向和反向传播书中列出的是什么
is what's listed in the book on forward and backward propagation 136
on forward and backward propagation 136 art with a lot of time but we can now
很多时间的艺术，但我们现在可以放松
art with a lot of time but we can now relax
relax really and going another presentation
真的要去另一个演讲
好的
relax really and going another presentation
okay
所以我真的很想让你知道后空翻并讨论有关
so I really want to you know do good backflips and discuss about the
backflips and discuss about the elementary thinks about Markov models
关于马尔可夫模型的初步思考，并在讨论过程中
elementary thinks about Markov models and in the process of course discussing
and in the process of course discussing the sentimental things we receive
感性的事情，我们收到了不同的实现
the sentimental things we receive different implementations of this
different implementations of this forward and market messages but they
转发和市场消息，但他们希望本次讲座的准确性
forward and market messages but they want the precision of this lectures as
want the precision of this lectures as part of for doing you know built a
您知道的一部分使用概率图形建立了仿真
part of for doing you know built a simulation using probabilistic graphical
simulation using probabilistic graphical models and actually some of you are
模型，实际上你们中的一些人对项目感兴趣，就可以
models and actually some of you are interested on on projects right you can
interested on on projects right you can see welcome to slice and start your own
看到欢迎分割并开始您自己的作品，那么他们可能会非常
see welcome to slice and start your own works then they can be lots of very
works then they can be lots of very complicated see the map of northern
复杂，请参见具有多个多重变量的北岸状态空间模型的地图
complicated see the map of northern shore state-space models with multiple
shore state-space models with multiple change that they are interacting with
改变了彼此之间交互的复杂性
change that they are interacting with each other with a lot of complexity with
each other with a lot of complexity with observation notice that there the
观察注意到，那里的可能性模是非线性的，所以如果你
observation notice that there the likelihood mods are nonlinear so if you
likelihood mods are nonlinear so if you can do lots of fancy things with it
可以用它做很多花哨的事情，所以不仅是我尝试时的野心
can do lots of fancy things with it alright so not only ambition when I try
alright so not only ambition when I try to do through the very elementary things
当某些东西只有一个时，要通过最基本的事情来做
to do through the very elementary things when something will only have
when something will only have discussions I'm going to bypass it but
讨论，我将绕过它，但是您有机会离开它
discussions I'm going to bypass it but you have an opportunity to to leave that
you have an opportunity to to leave that again but when there's something in this
再说一次，但是当这个东西中有什么东西的时候，即使它是
again but when there's something in this one that we haven't seen it even if it's
one that we haven't seen it even if it's trivial we would spend something
琐碎的我们会花一些时间
trivial we would spend something sometime
好吧，你可能会问我为什么我们要去这个
all right so you may ask me why do we go this
so you may ask me why do we go this backwards now to do these things you
现在倒退做这些事情，你知道的，因为我们有我完成的奢侈品
backwards now to do these things you know because we have the luxury I finish
know because we have the luxury I finish covering the course so now I can just
涵盖整个课程，所以现在我可以尽情玩乐，这是因为如果我们
covering the course so now I can just have fun right that's all because if we
have fun right that's all because if we go other ways and we do Junction tree
走其他方式，我们在五月做结点树算法，那么你说什么是
go other ways and we do Junction tree algorithm in May then you say what is
algorithm in May then you say what is going on here right there yeah all right
在这里继续，是的，没事
也许您应该录制“是的”权利，以便您可以播放录音机说“是的”
algorithm in May then you say what is going on here right there yeah all right
maybe you should record the yes right so you can play recorder say yeah what
也许您应该录制“是的”权利，以便您可以播放录音机说“是的”
you can play recorder say yeah what basically considering a collection of
基本上考虑了指标L中的随机变量的集合
basically considering a collection of random variables for the index L in the
random variables for the index L in the corner angle systems means time okay but
转角系统意味着时间还可以，但是您还有很多其他地方
corner angle systems means time okay but many other things where you have
many other things where you have sequences of random variables has
随机变量序列与时间无关，好吧，它不在
sequences of random variables has nothing to do with time okay it's not in
nothing to do with time okay it's not in the spatial location you know each other
你们彼此了解的空间位置，所以我们假设
the spatial location you know each other so we are assuming that somehow in our
so we are assuming that somehow in our model we have the cumulative
模型，我们有累积分布，可以在这里
model we have the cumulative distribution okay and here in this place
distribution okay and here in this place I'm interested on a finite joint
我对不推的有限联合累积分布感兴趣
I'm interested on a finite joint cumulative distribution I'm not pushing
cumulative distribution I'm not pushing this train basically to infinity because
这列火车基本上是无穷远的，因为不是他们带来了其他问题，
this train basically to infinity because not they bring other issues that we
not they bring other issues that we don't want to deal at this point so the
不想在这一点上处理，所以第一个兴趣量是定义
don't want to deal at this point so the first quantity of interest is to define
first quantity of interest is to define what we call a stationary process and
我们称之为平稳过程的能力是
what we call a stationary process and the ability is if we already have
the ability is if we already have defined the CDF like this a stationary
像这样定义CDF的固定过程就是所谓的联合
defined the CDF like this a stationary process is the one called this joint
process is the one called this joint distribution is equal to this where
分配等于此，而不是1我有1加tau
distribution is equal to this where instead of 1 I have 1 plus tau
instead of 1 I have 1 plus tau sort of - 2 plus tau etc so basically as
有点-2加tau等，所以基本上当我用tau拉伸整个东西时，我可以
sort of - 2 plus tau etc so basically as I stretch the whole thing by tau I can
I stretch the whole thing by tau I can still get the same joint cumulative
仍然获得相同的联合累积分布函数
still get the same joint cumulative distribution function
distribution function now the familiar model that we used in
现在涉及到我们在现在的课程中使用的熟悉的模型
now the familiar model that we used in the class of now is involved about
the class of now is involved about convey an assumption that tastes
传达一个假设，该假设基本上尝到了xn加1的概率
convey an assumption that tastes basically the probability of xn plus 1
basically the probability of xn plus 1 depends only on the values of xn and not
仅取决于xn的值，而不取决于先前的值，好，很多书
depends only on the values of xn and not on the previous values ok and many books
on the previous values ok and many books have been written on this topic in the
您已经在乐观建模的背景下写过关于这个主题的文章
have been written on this topic in the context of optimistic modeling you know
context of optimistic modeling you know molecular simulations financial
分子模拟，金融工程等，但我可以告诉你
molecular simulations financial engineering etc but I can tell you that
engineering etc but I can tell you that everyone recent sort of research paper
大家最近卖出的研究论文，他们都说这个话题是
everyone recent sort of research paper you sell the topic they say now this is
you sell the topic they say now this is not very good ok so somehow you need to
不太好，所以您需要摆脱这种假设，我们摆脱
not very good ok so somehow you need to get rid of this assumption we get rid of
get rid of this assumption we get rid of it for now
现在就可以了，所以现在我们基本上要从
it for now ok so now we are going to basically from
ok so now we are going to basically from natural - processing and actually you
自然-处理，实际上，当您读回书时，您会看到书是第一本书
natural - processing and actually you will see when you read back is book one
will see when you read back is book one of the things you can do is if you take
您可以做的事情是，如果您将文本和单词序列
of the things you can do is if you take a text and the sequence of words in the
a text and the sequence of words in the text right you can think of that as the
文本权利，您可以将其视为动力系统，从本质上讲，您可以
text right you can think of that as the dynamical system and in essence you can
dynamical system and in essence you can write an essay you can write the
写一篇论文，你可以用计算机程序来写作业，
write an essay you can write the homework with a computer program where
homework with a computer program where you know it randomly selects words from
您知道它使用前一个单词从字典中随机选择单词
you know it randomly selects words from the dictionary using the previous words
the dictionary using the previous words and you submit a whole paper but it's a
您提交了整篇论文，但这是计算机助手，我相信
and you submit a whole paper but it's a computer mate right and and I am sure
computer mate right and and I am sure lots of people do that ok this day so
今天很多人都会这样做，所以有趣的是，如果您使用的是Mac
lots of people do that ok this day so that is interesting is if you use a Mac
that is interesting is if you use a Mac avianna function and the product rule
avianna功能和产品规则可以立即看到简化
avianna function and the product rule you can see the immediate simplification
you can see the immediate simplification right so you can see here giving X 3
正确，所以您可以在这里看到根据X 1和X 2给出X 3，您只有X
right so you can see here giving X 3 depending on X 1 and X 2 you have only X
depending on X 1 and X 2 you have only X 3 depending on X 2 X 2 and XT minus 12
3取决于X 2 X 2和XT减去12，因此您需要保留的变量
3 depending on X 2 X 2 and XT minus 12 so the variables that you need to keep
so the variables that you need to keep track of if each of this is
跟踪这是否是同性恋价值观，您知道自己只有一个
track of if each of this is gay values you know you only have just a
gay values you know you only have just a stage for its XP this time matrices of
这次，它的XP舞台上的K平方量级矩阵正确，所以这是
stage for its XP this time matrices of the order of K square right so this is
the order of K square right so this is way much less complexity to be done it
没有他们的马尔可夫假设就可以做到的复杂度要低得多
way much less complexity to be done it without them Markovian assumption okay
without them Markovian assumption okay [Applause]
[鼓掌]所以我们确定这个问题是
[Applause] so we are sure that this problem is the
so we are sure that this problem is the mode of the gives me the evolution of
的模式给了我状态的演变
mode of the gives me the evolution of the state
the state if you expressly parametrically then we
如果您明确表示参数化，那么我们假设
if you expressly parametrically then we assume that but then the parameters to
assume that but then the parameters to that model don't change with time okay
该模型不会随着时间的推移而改变，通常来说，它试图计算
that model don't change with time okay and generally speaking trying to compute
and generally speaking trying to compute the parameters in this model is known as
该模型中的参数无疑是一个琐碎的问题，所以您知道
the parameters in this model is known as certainly a trivial problem so you know
certainly a trivial problem so you know when you have you try to model something
例如，当您尝试使用马尔可夫链对某些事物进行建模时，如果
when you have you try to model something with a Markov chain for example and if
with a Markov chain for example and if you make this amount I only distribution
你使这个数额我只分配例如这样的东西，你知道
you make this amount I only distribution for example something like that you know
for example something like that you know you are going to have a lot of unknowns
在定义此分布时，您将有很多未知数，并且
you are going to have a lot of unknowns in defining this distribution and the
in defining this distribution and the only way to compute them is by using
计算它们的唯一方法是使用数据，因此，如果您知道可以
only way to compute them is by using data alright so if you know you can do
data alright so if you know you can do much more active with estimation what as
更加积极地估计我们认为通过EM实施的内容
much more active with estimation what as we consider implemented through the EM
we consider implemented through the EM algorithm or maybe do a mapping but then
算法，或者做一个映射，但是假设您从它开始，不，您
algorithm or maybe do a mapping but then assume that you start with it no you
assume that you start with it no you have to learn this and then cook is not
必须学习这一点，然后煮不是被老鼠的预测影响
have to learn this and then cook is not being predictions influence of the rat
being predictions influence of the rat okay so we only assume that xn plus 1
好吧，所以我们只假设xn加1个差分xn，但是您以哪种方式
okay so we only assume that xn plus 1 differential xn but in which way you
differential xn but in which way you know what is this table that's something
知道这张桌子是做什么的
know what is this table that's something to do
艾滋病毒，所以您在这里看到的基本上就是我们为此描述的
for HIV so what you see here is basically what we described for the this
basically what we described for the this is this impression you see on the bottom
您在底部看到的这种印象基本上是Cleary的
is this impression you see on the bottom is basically the Cleary's out what the
is basically the Cleary's out what the Montpellier assumption is used right and
正确使用蒙彼利埃假设，这是我们可以从中得到的东西
Montpellier assumption is used right and this is what allow us to go from and the
this is what allow us to go from and the composition that depends for XP depends
XP所依赖的组成在一定程度上取决于所有先前的变量
composition that depends for XP depends on all the previous variables to extent
on all the previous variables to extent it depends only on X 3 minus 1 okay you
它仅取决于X 3减1好的，您可以采用更好的方法，因为我们正在谈论
it depends only on X 3 minus 1 okay you can a better way since we're talking
can a better way since we're talking about published graphical models you can
关于已发布的图形模型，您可以立即看到给定X 2 X 1和X
about published graphical models you can see immediately that given X 2 X 1 and X
see immediately that given X 2 X 1 and X 3 are independent right so when you
3是独立的权利，因此当您写给定X 1时X 3的概率
3 are independent right so when you write the probability of X 3 given X 1
write the probability of X 3 given X 1 and X 2 that you get here you can get
和X 2到达此处，您可以在X 2正确的情况下摆脱X 1，因为它们
and X 2 that you get here you can get rid of X 1 given X 2 right because they
rid of X 1 given X 2 right because they are independent I think because of the
是独立的，我认为因为分离还可以，所以你知道会是2
are independent I think because of the separation okay so you know will be 2 so
separation okay so you know will be 2 so we like us rhabdo
我们喜欢我们rhabdo立即将此图形模型
we like us rhabdo this this graphical model immediately
this this graphical model immediately implies that the question ok all right
意味着这个问题好吧，所以给定X 2 X 1和X 3是独立的
implies that the question ok all right so given X 2 X 1 and X 3 are independent
so given X 2 X 1 and X 3 are independent you can all right so let me keep going
你可以的，所以让我继续走下去，假设这个矩阵你知道
you can all right so let me keep going so this matrix you know assuming that
so this matrix you know assuming that the states of the script we are going to
脚本的状态，我们将其称为ALJ矩阵，然后
the states of the script we are going to call this an ALJ matrix right and
call this an ALJ matrix right and eventually we have to find some way to
最终我们必须找到某种方法来从数据中进行计算，所以这有点
eventually we have to find some way to compute from data ok so this is sort of
compute from data ok so this is sort of our state transition diagram that you
我们的状态转换图，您可以基本上证明这一点
our state transition diagram that you can demonstrate basically this
can demonstrate basically this probabilities circuit with some
概率电路，带有一些类似的示意图，因此您
probabilities circuit with some schematic that looks like that so you
schematic that looks like that so you know here there is a self transition
知道这里有从状态1回到状态1的自转移概率
know here there is a self transition probability from state 1 back to state 1
probability from state 1 back to state 1 transition state 2 but no to state 3 and
过渡状态2，但不过渡到状态3，并且在状态3中注意，基本上没有
transition state 2 but no to state 3 and notice in state 3 basically there is no
notice in state 3 basically there is no way you can escape because the
您可以逃脱的方式，因为回到状态3的可能性是
way you can escape because the probability of being back to state 3 is
probability of being back to state 3 is 1 right so this is sort of an
1对，所以在此图中，这是一个有趣的情况
1 right so this is sort of an interesting case in this diagram you
interesting case in this diagram you will not be
不会从三个逃脱然后回到一个
will not be from three to escape and go back to one
from three to escape and go back to one and two okay all right
还有两个还好吧，所以在这种情况下的转移矩阵是
and two okay all right so the transition matrix in this case is
so the transition matrix in this case is a 1 1 a 1 2 A 2 2 a 2 3 and 1
a 1 1 a 1 2 A 2 2 a 2 3和1孔这是一个选择，而且更多
a 1 1 a 1 2 A 2 2 a 2 3 and 1 well that's a choice and more
well that's a choice and more interesting transition matrix square we
有趣的过渡矩阵平方，我们可以进行自我过渡，所以这是
interesting transition matrix square we have self transition okay and so this is
have self transition okay and so this is best in transition from state 1 the
从状态1过渡到地图1到状态2的最佳过渡
best in transition from state 1 the first roll to map to state 1 state 2
first roll to map to state 1 state 2 state 3 so this probabilities have to
状态3，因此此概率必须加起来为1，您会注意到每次损失该怎么办
state 3 so this probabilities have to sum to 1 you notice every loss how to do
sum to 1 you notice every loss how to do one and in this case that say we are
一个，在这种情况下，说我们歪曲了初始概率
one and in this case that say we are skewing that the probability of initial
skewing that the probability of initial state is given as 1 3 1 3 1 3 so if best
状态给出为1 3 1 3 1 3因此，如果最好的话，处于其他任何状态的机会均等
state is given as 1 3 1 3 1 3 so if best an equal chance of being in any other
an equal chance of being in any other state thank you
状态谢谢你从这个状态开始
state thank you you start with the state with this
you start with the state with this probability this is your initial
这是你的初始概率，我请你告诉我
probability this is your initial probability and I ask you to tell me
probability and I ask you to tell me what's going to happen long term to
长期会发生什么，以计算在
what's going to happen long term to calculate the probability of being at
calculate the probability of being at the given state after into a time how
一段时间后的给定状态您将如何实施
the given state after into a time how are you going to implement this just in
are you going to implement this just in three lines quote so let me give you
三行报价，所以让我给你，我给你这个过渡
three lines quote so let me give you this and I give you this transition
this and I give you this transition matrix and I'm asked them to compute for
矩阵，我被要求他们为我计算我们知道的概率
matrix and I'm asked them to compute for me what we you know the probability of
me what we you know the probability of being in state 1 state 2 state 3 is
处于状态1状态2状态3将处于时间无穷大
being in state 1 state 2 state 3 is going to be at time infinity
going to be at time infinity assuming that have somehow this chain
假设这个链以某种方式收敛了，那么我该如何实现
assuming that have somehow this chain converges okay so how do i implement
converges okay so how do i implement this we may struggle a little but it's
这个我们可能会有点挣扎，但这是在网上做的
this we may struggle a little but it's been online that does this
一步而不是
step rather than
您将开始在不同的州继续前进，
you're gonna start moving on this on different states right with the
different states right with the dynamical model apply by a so I'm gonna
动态模型由a来应用，所以我要编写软件来做到这一点，那该怎么办
dynamical model apply by a so I'm gonna write the software to do that so what do
write the software to do that so what do you have to do the first step
你必须要做的第一步
是的，非常好，非常好
write the software to do that so what do you have to do the first step
exactly yeah very good excellent
我必须给出正确的反馈，所以他们认为我对课堂反应很好
I have to give feedback right so they think am i responding to the class okay
think am i responding to the class okay so what do we do
那么我们该怎么办
所以我们基本上必须从这个概率中选择一些要开始的东西，
think am i responding to the class okay so what do we do
so we basically have to select with this probabilities something to start and
所以我们基本上必须从这个概率中选择一些要开始的东西，
probabilities something to start and then assuming that say we select the
然后假设说我们选择第二种状态，那么我们将不得不
then assuming that say we select the second state then we're going to have to
second state then we're going to have to select with this probabilities to what's
从这种可能性中选择从状态一开始的良好过渡，然后我们
select with this probabilities to what's a good transition from state one and we
a good transition from state one and we make transition with this to take one
进行此过渡，以向后退以进入状态3的两个，并且
make transition with this to take one backward to take two of state three and
backward to take two of state three and then keep repeating this with the hope
然后继续重复，希望在一天结束时我们能够
then keep repeating this with the hope that somehow at the end of the day we're
that somehow at the end of the day we're gonna reach some stationary distribution
会达到一些固定分布，我们将只介绍十二个
gonna reach some stationary distribution and we will introduce twelve only one
and we will introduce twelve only one stationary distribution for this Markov
这个马尔可夫链的平稳分布现在存在，你能告诉我我的意思吗？
stationary distribution for this Markov chains exist now can you tell me I mean
chains exist now can you tell me I mean this is something we are keenly covered
这是我们希望在讲座中涵盖的内容，希望也许是，但是如果
this is something we are keenly covered on lectures in hope maybe but if
on lectures in hope maybe but if somebody gives you this distribution and
有人给你这个分布，并说这个分布的样本怎么做
somebody gives you this distribution and say sample from this distribution how do
say sample from this distribution how do we do this how do something from a given
我们这样做是如何根据给定的分布来做某事，而您知道自己是
we do this how do something from a given distribution and you know that you are
distribution and you know that you are on screen so you should have suffered
在屏幕上，所以你应该遭受这个痛苦，你可以准确地知道会发生什么
on screen so you should have suffered from this can you tell exactly what will
from this can you tell exactly what will lead you to say among state for your
引导您在州之间说出自己的状态
lead you to say among state for your state to
我们要上网吗
are we gonna do up in online
因此，来自此分布的原始样本中的一些分布
so the original sample from this distribution some of the distribution
我的意思是你要如何从离散分布中采样
I mean how do you sample from discrete distribution that's what I'm asking
distribution that's what I'm asking that's the single thing to sample from
这是从离散分布中采样的唯一方法
that's the single thing to sample from discrete distribution
看到制服上的东西，假设从零到一，如果是
see there's something from a uniform and let's say from zero to one and if it
let's say from zero to one and if it happens to be let's say hi and then
碰巧是打个招呼，然后指向六点六点或几点，然后您说
happens to be let's say hi and then point six six or something then you say
point six six or something then you say you are now on state three all right
如果您高于点，您现在同样处于状态三
you are now on state three all right similarly if you are higher than point
similarly if you are higher than point three three but less than that then your
三三，但比那少，那么你的状态2等好吧，这就是你的方式
three three but less than that then your state 2 etc okay so this is how you
state 2 etc okay so this is how you sample from discrete distribution since
离散分布的样本，因为我们定义了该转移概率a
sample from discrete distribution since we defined this transition probability a
we defined this transition probability a I J what we often use and the location
IJ我们经常使用的位置也是该过渡的LJ
I J what we often use and the location is also a LJ for this transition
is also a LJ for this transition probability basically transition is from
基本上从I过渡到J的概率
probability basically transition is from I to J
I to J but in n steps the idea being is that
但是在n步中，想法是您从时间T开始于状态I和之后的状态
but in n steps the idea being is that you start at time T at state I and after
you start at time T at state I and after n steps even and yourself in state Z so
甚至n步并且您自己处于状态Z，所以这是N步过渡
n steps even and yourself in state Z so this is the N step transition
this is the N step transition probability and effectively this
概率并有效地满足了联邦方程，即
probability and effectively this satisfies the Commonwealth equation that
satisfies the Commonwealth equation that what you have seen it in many different
在本课程中，您在LD的许多不同背景中看到了什么，因此您可以
what you have seen it in many different contexts in LD in this course so you can
contexts in LD in this course so you can think if you want transition in M plus n
想想如果您想在M加n的步骤中从I过渡到J，您能做的就是
think if you want transition in M plus n steps from I to J that you can do is you
steps from I to J that you can do is you can transition them steps decay for a
可以在可能的情况下将它们过渡为逐步衰减，然后在其余情况下
can transition them steps decay for a possible case and then in the remaining
possible case and then in the remaining n steps transition from K today
今天从K过渡n步，所以英联邦方程基本上
n steps transition from K today so the Commonwealth equation basically
so the Commonwealth equation basically looks like that ok and increased for
看起来不错，并为此增加，使您可以写出自己知道的n
looks like that ok and increased for this allows you to write you know this n
this allows you to write you know this n step transition matrix the way that you
逐步过渡矩阵，就像您在这里看到的一样，所以不要
step transition matrix the way that you see here okay so don't sort of the
see here okay so don't sort of the liberal interpretation of this because
对此的自由解释，因为对此for的解释是
liberal interpretation of this because the interpretation of this for is
the interpretation of this for is basically the Commonwealth equation that
基本上，那里的英联邦方程式
basically the Commonwealth equation that which is there
我认为这个问题很难解决，但是您可以在图片上看到
I think this problems are very difficult but you can see in on the picture on the
but you can see in on the picture on the bottom for example that you know after a
例如，您需要经过几个步骤才能知道底部，因为我们需要初始化
bottom for example that you know after a few steps because we need to initialize
few steps because we need to initialize things the state explored now depends on
现在探索的状态取决于X 3但也取决于X 2和X 1因此
things the state explored now depends on X 3 but also depends on X 2 and X 1 so
X 3 but also depends on X 2 and X 1 so this is the Markov chain basically or
这基本上是马尔可夫链，还是感谢流程，所以这有点
this is the Markov chain basically or thanks flow so this is a way a little
thanks flow so this is a way a little bit more complicated problem and so you
有点复杂的问题，所以您保持跟踪依赖基本上是
bit more complicated problem and so you keep track dependence is basically that
keep track dependence is basically that the grab back from X for X 1
从X抢回X 1
好吧，它说你知道我现在想做的这个例子了
keep track dependence is basically that the grab back from X for X 1
well it said you know what myself now I want to do this example
好吧，它说你知道我现在想做的这个例子了
want to do this example so he just described and we will
所以他只是描述了，我们将在下周继续，我将
so he just described and we will continue on this next week and I will
continue on this next week and I will put the notes played tomorrow so you can
把明天玩的音符放好，这样你就可以阅读了，所以音符是
put the notes played tomorrow so you can read it all right so the notes is
read it all right so the notes is basically to try to build a probability
基本上是试图建立一个写语言的概率模型
basically to try to build a probability model for writing a language speaking
model for writing a language speaking language okay so the idea is you know
语言还可以，所以您的想法是您知道我们将不得不分配一些
language okay so the idea is you know we're going to have to assign some
we're going to have to assign some probability for each word and you can
每个单词的概率，您可以将其视为美丽的概率
probability for each word and you can take it to be beautiful some probability
take it to be beautiful some probability from transition from one world to
从一个世界过渡到另一个世界，这是二元概率
from transition from one world to another this is the bigram probability
another this is the bigram probability and then a transition from two previous
然后从先前的两个单词过渡到第三世界好了，这样您就可以
and then a transition from two previous words to a third world okay so you can
words to a third world okay so you can actually use this if you build model for
如果您为此构建模型，则实际使用它，这意味着您必须学习
actually use this if you build model for this which means you have to learn the
this which means you have to learn the parameters from this from given spoken
您可以实际使用的给定英语口语或文本中的参数
parameters from this from given spoken English or text you can actually use
English or text you can actually use this to complete the sentence and this
这是为了完成句子，这个巴里在我小时候就被告知
this to complete the sentence and this Barry I was told when I was young it's
Barry I was told when I was young it's very polite to complete the sentence or
很礼貌地完成句子或父亲的权利，当我教我的时候
very polite to complete the sentence or Father's right it seems when I teach I
Father's right it seems when I teach I do that all the time remember
一直这样做，请记住我只是完成了我说的句子
do that all the time remember I just complete the sentence that I say
I just complete the sentence that I say thank you so that's not very polite okay
谢谢，所以这不是很礼貌，不是开玩笑，您可以实际使用它
thank you so that's not very polite okay and not a joke you can actually use this
and not a joke you can actually use this to write document you know once you
一旦开始就编写您知道的文档，它会学习这种过渡
to write document you know once you start it and it learns this transition
start it and it learns this transition probabilities you can start picking up a
您可以使用之前的单词开始随机挑选单词的概率
probabilities you can start picking up a random words using the previous ones
random words using the previous ones arranging you have a whole document and
安排您有一个完整的文档，也许您会喜欢的，所以
arranging you have a whole document and and maybe you will like that okay so
and maybe you will like that okay so this have how these transition
这些过渡概率看起来像这样，所以这是
this have how these transition probabilities would look like so this is
probabilities would look like so this is for the probabilities of different
字母表中不同字母的概率
for the probabilities of different letters in the alphabet
letters in the alphabet okay
好的，系统已经通过
okay and the system this has been computed by
and the system this has been computed by using a given a textbook and these are
使用给定的教科书，这些是传记的概率
using a given a textbook and these are the Biograph probabilities that gives
the Biograph probabilities that gives you the transition from one letter to
你从一个字母到另一个字母的过渡，就像一个人类图
you the transition from one letter to another this is like a human diagram
another this is like a human diagram that maybe you have seen it in
也许您已经在这种振动概率的呈现中看到了它
that maybe you have seen it in presentation of this vibro probability
presentation of this vibro probability in other contexts so the bigger this Y
在其他情况下，这个Y点越大，则出现的可能性越高
in other contexts so the bigger this Y dot the higher the probability so
dot the higher the probability so obviously you're not going to go from a
显然，您不会从变成作家的可能性很小
obviously you're not going to go from a to a writer has very low probability
to a writer has very low probability from a 12 you know and if you look from
从12知道，如果从n2i看，那很重要
from a 12 you know and if you look from n2i that's significant
n2i that's significant okay because they have too many nicolas
好吧，因为他们周围有太多尼古拉斯，好尼克好吧，那又怎样
okay because they have too many nicolas around right Nick all right okay so what
around right Nick all right okay so what I want to tell you and we just thing is
我想告诉你，我们只是事情在那儿，我要你告诉我们如何
I want to tell you and we just thing is there I want you to tell how we're
there I want you to tell how we're actually going to use a document to
实际上将使用文档来计算此转移概率
actually going to use a document to compute this transition probabilities
compute this transition probabilities and we're gonna use maximum likelihood
我们将尽最大可能做到这一点
and we're gonna use maximum likelihood to do that all right
to do that all right so effectively the calculation will be
因此，有效的计算将是对
so effectively the calculation will be sort of an elementary introduction to
sort of an elementary introduction to the way we're going to be map estimation
我们将要为状态空间模型进行地图估计的方式，因此我们将
the way we're going to be map estimation for state space model so we're going to
for state space model so we're going to achieve this in the Delta national
在三角洲国家速度上实现这一目标，这种类型的影响是什么
achieve this in the Delta national velocity what is the effect of this type
velocity what is the effect of this type of Emily estimate when you have limited
艾米丽（Emily）的人估计您的数据有限时，因为我没有保湿霜
of Emily estimate when you have limited data so because moisturisers I don't
data so because moisturisers I don't have more than two
有两个以上